[
    {
        "question": "In what fictional city is the TV show Futurama set?",
        "correct_answer": " New New York",
        "answer_a": " New Chicago",
        "answer_b": " New New York",
        "answer_c": " New San Francisco",
        "answer_d": " None of these"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the lowest ranking species in the Covenant hierarchy in the Halo series?",
        "correct_answer": " Grunt",
        "answer_a": " Drone",
        "answer_b": " Brute",
        "answer_c": " Elite",
        "answer_d": " Grunt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who controls the Flood in the Halo series?",
        "correct_answer": " Gravemind",
        "answer_a": " Gravemind",
        "answer_b": " The Prophet of Truth",
        "answer_c": " The Arbiter",
        "answer_d": " No one"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a SPARTAN in the Halo series?",
        "correct_answer": " All of these",
        "answer_a": " A Genetically modified super soldier",
        "answer_b": " A higher ranking soldier than a ODST",
        "answer_c": " Troopers that went through military training at the age of five",
        "answer_d": " All of these"
    },
    {
        "question": "What species is the Didact in the Halo series?",
        "correct_answer": " Forerunner",
        "answer_a": " Forerunner",
        "answer_b": " Precursor",
        "answer_c": " Promethean",
        "answer_d": " Yamne"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Halo series, Zealots use Energy Swords.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following does the UNSC use to transport troops in the halo series?",
        "correct_answer": " Pelicans",
        "answer_a": " Falcons",
        "answer_b": " Hornets",
        "answer_c": " Phantoms",
        "answer_d": " Pelicans"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does UNSC stand for in the Halo series?",
        "correct_answer": " United Nations Space Command",
        "answer_a": " None of the above",
        "answer_b": " United Nations Space Council",
        "answer_c": " United Nations Space Command",
        "answer_d": " Unified Nations Supreme Court"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest UNSC ship in the Halo series?",
        "correct_answer": " UNSC Infinity",
        "answer_a": " UNSC In Amber Clad",
        "answer_b": " UNSC Infinity",
        "answer_c": " UNSC Spirit of Fire",
        "answer_d": " UNSC Pillar of Autumn"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city does Halo 3 ODST take place in?",
        "correct_answer": " New Mombasa",
        "answer_a": " Voi",
        "answer_b": " New Mombasa",
        "answer_c": " Toronto",
        "answer_d": " New York"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest species of the Covenant in the Halo series?",
        "correct_answer": " Hunter",
        "answer_a": " Brute",
        "answer_b": " Hunter",
        "answer_c": " Jackal",
        "answer_d": " Elite"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who made the fictional Mother Brain and for what purpose?",
        "correct_answer": " The Chozo built her to be a organic Supercomputer.",
        "answer_a": " The Galactic Federation built her as a next generation Aurora Unit.",
        "answer_b": " It is unknown who made her but she was made to control Zebes.",
        "answer_c": " The Space Pirates built her to be one of their generals.",
        "answer_d": " The Chozo built her to be a organic Supercomputer."
    },
    {
        "question": "How did the Alimbics become extinct in the Metroid series?",
        "correct_answer": " The entire species used up their life energy to imprison Gorea.",
        "answer_a": " They discovered Phazon and developed Phazon Madness causing them to wipe each other out.",
        "answer_b": " Gorea wiped them out.",
        "answer_c": " The entire species used up their life energy to imprison Gorea.",
        "answer_d": " The Metroids wiped them out."
    },
    {
        "question": "What creature passes on the X Parasite to Samus in the Metroid series?",
        "correct_answer": " Hornoad",
        "answer_a": " Metroid",
        "answer_b": " Space Pirate",
        "answer_c": " Kihunter",
        "answer_d": " Hornoad"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the Deleter in the Metroid series?",
        "correct_answer": " James Pierce",
        "answer_a": " Lyle Smithsonian",
        "answer_b": " Adam Malkovich",
        "answer_c": " K.G Misawa",
        "answer_d": " James Pierce"
    },
    {
        "question": "Kraid is the only one of his species encountered in the Metroid game.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do Steamlords keep as pets in the Metroid series of games?",
        "correct_answer": " Vaporwing",
        "answer_a": " Steambot",
        "answer_b": " Warp Hound",
        "answer_c": " Steamspider",
        "answer_d": " Vaporwing"
    },
    {
        "question": "An ancient Chozo prophecy predicts the coming of Phazon and the Metroid Prime. In this prophecy the Metroid Prime is referred to as which of the following?",
        "correct_answer": " Worm",
        "answer_a": " Worm",
        "answer_b": " Beast",
        "answer_c": " Destroyer",
        "answer_d": " Consumer"
    },
    {
        "question": "King Worm can be fought after Mother Brainin Metroid Zero Mission.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What planet are Kihunters from in the Metroid games?",
        "correct_answer": " Unknown",
        "answer_a": " Space Pirate Homeworld",
        "answer_b": " Unknown",
        "answer_c": " SR388",
        "answer_d": " Zebes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What planet is Samus from  in the Metorid games?",
        "correct_answer": " K-2L",
        "answer_a": " It is unknown",
        "answer_b": " K-2L",
        "answer_c": " Norion",
        "answer_d": " Zebes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the enemy faction in the first N.O.V.A?",
        "correct_answer": " Xenos",
        "answer_a": " Xenos",
        "answer_b": " Volterites",
        "answer_c": " Judgers",
        "answer_d": " The Dominion"
    },
    {
        "question": "The N.O.V.A 3 Shotgun is both semi and fully automatic.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "On which planet does the first two missions in N.O.V.A 2 take place?",
        "correct_answer": " Aquarius",
        "answer_a": " Sagittarius",
        "answer_b": " Earth",
        "answer_c": " New Ceres",
        "answer_d": " Aquarius"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who helps Kal Wardin find the Judger artifact aboard Therrius in N.O.V.A?",
        "correct_answer": " MazRah",
        "answer_a": " Prometheus",
        "answer_b": " Yelena",
        "answer_c": " MazRah",
        "answer_d": " Rufus"
    },
    {
        "question": "In N.O.V.A, Kal Wardin is rewarded for finding out what happened aboard the Colonial Pride by almost being killed.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the leader of the Volterites in N.O.V.A?",
        "correct_answer": " The Overseer",
        "answer_a": " MazRah",
        "answer_b": " None of the above",
        "answer_c": " Prometheus",
        "answer_d": " The Overseer"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Xeno is capable of teleporting in N.O.V.A?",
        "correct_answer": " Heavy Demon",
        "answer_a": " Heavy Demon",
        "answer_b": " Red Demon",
        "answer_c": " Imp",
        "answer_d": " Fiend"
    },
    {
        "question": "In N.O.V.A, President Folson is unarmed.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Boreas is the only desert planet in the N.O.V.A series.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the damsel you have to save in the classic arcade game Donkey Kong?",
        "correct_answer": " Pauline",
        "answer_a": " Peach",
        "answer_b": " Daisy",
        "answer_c": " Pauline",
        "answer_d": " Dixie Kong"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these was a name that game character, Mario, was once called?",
        "correct_answer": " Jumpman",
        "answer_a": " Koopa",
        "answer_b": " Plumberio",
        "answer_c": " Jumpman",
        "answer_d": " Luigi"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who or what turned Warios treasure into monsters in the game, Wario World?",
        "correct_answer": " The black jewel",
        "answer_a": " Kemmy Koopa",
        "answer_b": " Lemmy Koopa",
        "answer_c": " The black jewel",
        "answer_d": " Bowser"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Mario games, what animal is a paratroopa?",
        "correct_answer": " A turtle",
        "answer_a": " A bird",
        "answer_b": " A lizard",
        "answer_c": " A turtle",
        "answer_d": " A tiger"
    },
    {
        "question": "When first created, Mario game character, Birdo, was what?",
        "correct_answer": " A boy",
        "answer_a": " A dog",
        "answer_b": " A boy",
        "answer_c": " A girl",
        "answer_d": " A bird"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the video games of Mario, is Luigi Marios cousin?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Mario video games, Bowser is the king of what?",
        "correct_answer": " Koopas",
        "answer_a": " Bowsers",
        "answer_b": " The Jungle",
        "answer_c": " Mushroom Kingdom",
        "answer_d": " Koopas"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the last boss in video game Paper Mario 2?",
        "correct_answer": " Shadow Queen",
        "answer_a": " Gloom Tail",
        "answer_b": " Bowser",
        "answer_c": " Shadow Queen",
        "answer_d": " Cackletta"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which movie is this Warcraft 3 quote from?",
        "answer_b": " Dirty Sanchez",
        "correct_answer": " Cool Hand Luke",
        "answer_a": " For a Fistful of Dollars",
        "answer_c": " Cool Hand Luke",
        "answer_d": " Metal Man"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where does the popular video game character Mario live?",
        "correct_answer": " The Mushroom Kingdom",
        "answer_a": " The Koopa Kingdom",
        "answer_b": " The Kingdom of Sarasaland",
        "answer_c": " The Mushroom Kingdom",
        "answer_d": " Yoshi Island"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Marios nationality according to Nintendo video games?",
        "correct_answer": " Italian",
        "answer_a": " Italian",
        "answer_b": " American",
        "answer_c": " Mexican",
        "answer_d": " British"
    },
    {
        "question": "Has the video game character Mario ever been in a TV show?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the first video game in which Mario appeared?",
        "correct_answer": " Donkey Kong",
        "answer_a": " Mario",
        "answer_b": " The Mario Bros.",
        "answer_c": " Super Mario",
        "answer_d": " Donkey Kong"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why does Mario wear a red cap in the Mario series of games?",
        "correct_answer": " The creators didnt have the technology to animate his hair.",
        "answer_a": " The creators didnt have the technology to animate his hair.",
        "answer_b": " He is bald.",
        "answer_c": " He cant make his hair neat.",
        "answer_d": " He likes his cap."
    },
    {
        "question": "Has Nintendo character Mario ever been a bad guy?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the Fire Flower do to Mario in the Mario video games?",
        "correct_answer": " Allows him to throw fire balls.",
        "answer_a": " Allows him to breath fire.",
        "answer_b": " Nothing",
        "answer_c": " It makes him angry.",
        "answer_d": " Allows him to throw fire balls."
    },
    {
        "question": "What effect does the Super Mushroom have on Mario in the popular series of video games?",
        "correct_answer": " It makes him bigger.",
        "answer_a": " It makes him bigger.",
        "answer_b": " None",
        "answer_c": " It makes him impervious to danger.",
        "answer_d": " It makes him smaller."
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Mario series of video games, Mario never uses any weapons.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Marios occupation in the Mario series of games?",
        "correct_answer": " plumber",
        "answer_a": " engineer",
        "answer_b": " doctor",
        "answer_c": " plumber",
        "answer_d": " electrician"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the land where most of the Legend of Zelda games take place?",
        "correct_answer": " Hyrule",
        "answer_a": " Hylia",
        "answer_b": " Hyrule",
        "answer_c": " Sacred Realm",
        "answer_d": " Termania"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which monster made its first appearance in the game The Legend of Zelda: Majoras Mask?",
        "correct_answer": " Chu-Chu",
        "answer_a": " Chu-Chu",
        "answer_b": " Armos",
        "answer_c": " Keese",
        "answer_d": " Octorok"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of the Legend of Zelda games does not feature the same Link as the others?",
        "correct_answer": " Wind Waker",
        "answer_a": " Ocarina of Time",
        "answer_b": " Links Awakening",
        "answer_c": " Wind Waker",
        "answer_d": " Majoras Mask"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not an item that Link uses in the Legend of Zelda series of games?",
        "correct_answer": " A spear used for immobilizing enemies",
        "answer_a": " A magical leaf used for flying",
        "answer_b": " A spear used for immobilizing enemies",
        "answer_c": " A jar that can suck stuff into it and shoot out gusts of wind",
        "answer_d": " A candle for shooting fire at enemies"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Legend of Zelda series of games Link has not worn a tunic in what colour?",
        "correct_answer": " yellow",
        "answer_a": " yellow",
        "answer_b": " blue",
        "answer_c": " red",
        "answer_d": " green"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which games were included in the 2003 Legend of Zelda Collectors edition that became available on the Nintendo GameCube?",
        "correct_answer": " The Legend of Zelda, The Adventure of Link, Ocarina of Time, Majoras Mask",
        "answer_a": " The Legenda of Zelda, The Adventure of Link, A Link to the Past, Ocarina of TIme",
        "answer_b": " Orcale of Seasons, Orcale of Ages, Links Awakening, and Minish Cap",
        "answer_c": " The Legend of Zelda, The Adventure of Link, Ocarina of Time, Majoras Mask",
        "answer_d": " A Link to the Past, Majoras Mask, Ocarina of Time, Wind Waker"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Final Fantasy 3 character is known for blitzes such as Bum Rush, Pummel, and Suplex?",
        "correct_answer": " Sabin",
        "answer_a": " Edgar",
        "answer_b": " Setzer",
        "answer_c": " Locke",
        "answer_d": " Sabin"
    },
    {
        "question": "What character from the Final Fantasy series used a weapon called the Buster Sword?",
        "correct_answer": " Cloud Strife",
        "answer_a": " Sephiroth",
        "answer_b": " Squall Leonhart",
        "answer_c": " Cloud Strife",
        "answer_d": " Seifer Almasy"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the summoned creatures that aided the characters in the Final Fantasy 8 game?",
        "correct_answer": " Guardian Forces",
        "answer_a": " Materia",
        "answer_b": " Summonings",
        "answer_c": " Espers",
        "answer_d": " Guardian Forces"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character was the main villain in the American Final Fantasy 3 game?",
        "correct_answer": " Kefka",
        "answer_a": " Sin",
        "answer_b": " Kefka",
        "answer_c": " Garland",
        "answer_d": " Sephiroth"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Final Fantasy game was released in North America on 7 September 1999?",
        "correct_answer": " Final Fantasy 8",
        "answer_a": " Final Fantasy 10",
        "answer_b": " Final Fantasy 9",
        "answer_c": " Final Fantasy 8",
        "answer_d": " Final Fantasy 7"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of these Final Fantasy characters didnt own an airship?",
        "correct_answer": " Rinoa Heartilly",
        "answer_a": " Setzer Gabbiani",
        "answer_b": " Daryl",
        "answer_c": " Rinoa Heartilly",
        "answer_d": " Cid Highwind"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year was the first Final Fantasy game released in Japan?",
        "correct_answer": " 1987",
        "answer_a": " 1989",
        "answer_b": " 1988",
        "answer_c": " 1990",
        "answer_d": " 1987"
    },
    {
        "question": "This character, who has appeared in nearly every Final Fantasy game, usually provides transportation to the main characters.",
        "correct_answer": " Cid",
        "answer_a": " Edgar",
        "answer_b": " Cid",
        "answer_c": " Sabin",
        "answer_d": " Squall"
    },
    {
        "question": "In this Final Fantasy spin-off every new recruit starts out as a Squire or a Chemist.",
        "correct_answer": " Final Fantasy Tactics",
        "answer_a": " Final Fantasy Mystic Quest",
        "answer_b": " Final Fantasy Tactics Advance",
        "answer_c": " Kingdom Hearts",
        "answer_d": " Final Fantasy Tactics"
    },
    {
        "question": "Final Fantasy X featured which mini-game?",
        "correct_answer": " Blitzball",
        "answer_a": " Snowboarding",
        "answer_b": " Blitzball",
        "answer_c": " Triple Triad",
        "answer_d": " Tetra Master"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which video game is the following quote from?",
        "correct_answer": " Escape from Monkey Island",
        "answer_a": " Escape from Monkey Island",
        "answer_b": " Simon the Sorcerer 3D",
        "answer_c": " Grim Fandango",
        "answer_d": " Monkey Island 2: LeChucks Revenge"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which video game are the following quotes from?",
        "answer_a": ": Come on, comrades! Up to the rooftop! Go!",
        "answer_b": " Call of Duty",
        "correct_answer": " Call of Duty",
        "answer_c": " Hidden and Dangerous 2",
        "answer_d": " Battlefield 1942"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the cheat for getting 50 000 simoleans in the computer game The Sims 2?",
        "correct_answer": " motherlode",
        "answer_a": " kaching",
        "answer_b": " all of these",
        "answer_c": " motherlode",
        "answer_d": " simoleons_$$$"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the expansion packs available for The Sims 2 game?",
        "correct_answer": " University, Night Life, Family Fun, Open for Business",
        "answer_a": " Odd Jobs, Pets",
        "answer_b": " All of these",
        "answer_c": " University, Night Life, Family Fun, Open for Business",
        "answer_d": " Makin Magic, Holiday, Party"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the computer game The Sims 2, in order for a Sim to have a baby, you must select the woohoo option on a different Sim.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "On the cover of the Sims 2 University expansion pack there is a picture of two Sims, one male and one female. What is the male Sim wearing?",
        "correct_answer": " toga",
        "answer_a": " hippie outfit",
        "answer_b": " toga",
        "answer_c": " mascot costume",
        "answer_d": " football equipment"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bella Goth is absent from the family when The Sims 2 begins.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Open for Business, the third expansion pack for The Sims 2, Sims may earn 25 business perks.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was the computer game The Sims 2 made solely by EA games?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Sims 2 game is rated E (Everyone).",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the robot in The Sims 2, that fetches take-away food?",
        "correct_answer": " MunchieBot",
        "answer_a": " HungryBot",
        "answer_b": " MunchieBot",
        "answer_c": " Bot",
        "answer_d": " FoodBot"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Nightlife, the second expansion pack for The Sims 2, Sims can have their own cars.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is not an actual die?",
        "correct_answer": " d18",
        "answer_a": " d10",
        "answer_b": " d100",
        "answer_c": " d4",
        "answer_d": " d18"
    },
    {
        "question": "This class has the ability to smite evil.",
        "correct_answer": " Paladin",
        "answer_a": " Rogue",
        "answer_b": " Paladin",
        "answer_c": " Ranger",
        "answer_d": " Sorcerer"
    },
    {
        "question": "This race doesnt sleep, they meditate instead.",
        "correct_answer": " Elf",
        "answer_a": " Dwarf",
        "answer_b": " Elf",
        "answer_c": " Human",
        "answer_d": " Changeling"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is not a feat?",
        "correct_answer": " Knowledge Arcana",
        "answer_a": " Quick Draw",
        "answer_b": " Knowledge Arcana",
        "answer_c": " Forge Ring",
        "answer_d": " Toughness"
    },
    {
        "question": "You roll a d20 for attack rolls (to see if you hit your opponent).",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which item costs the most according to the Players Handbook?",
        "correct_answer": " Full Plate Mail",
        "answer_a": " Whetstone",
        "answer_b": " Two-Bladed Sword",
        "answer_c": " Full Plate Mail",
        "answer_d": " Heavy Repeating Crossbow"
    },
    {
        "question": "How far can a medium sized, unencumbered creature walk in one round?",
        "correct_answer": " 30 feet",
        "answer_a": " 20 feet",
        "answer_b": " 50 feet",
        "answer_c": " 30 feet",
        "answer_d": " 10 feet"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which class casts arcane magic innately?",
        "correct_answer": " Sorcerer",
        "answer_a": " Ranger",
        "answer_b": " Cleric",
        "answer_c": " Wizard",
        "answer_d": " Sorcerer"
    },
    {
        "question": "This 9th level wizard spell is sought after by many characters as a reward.  Many wizards also strive to learn this spell.",
        "correct_answer": " Wish",
        "answer_a": " Power Word Kill",
        "answer_b": " Wish",
        "answer_c": " Imprisonment",
        "answer_d": " Gate"
    },
    {
        "question": "This class must choose 2 weapon fighting or archery as their weapon style at 2nd level.",
        "correct_answer": " Ranger",
        "answer_a": " Bard",
        "answer_b": " Cleric",
        "answer_c": " Ranger",
        "answer_d": " Fighter"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the first warp whistle located in the game Super Mario 3?",
        "correct_answer": " world 1-3",
        "answer_a": " world 1-3",
        "answer_b": " world 1 fortress",
        "answer_c": " world 2-5",
        "answer_d": " world 1-4"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Mario Kart: Double Dash, what is the last thing you unlock by getting gold in the all cup tour in mirror mode?",
        "correct_answer": " Parade car",
        "answer_a": " Parade car",
        "answer_b": " Bullet car",
        "answer_c": " Super Mario car",
        "answer_d": " Ganondorf car"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following characters can bounce off walls in the game Super Smash Brothers Melee?",
        "correct_answer": " Young Link",
        "answer_a": " Luigi",
        "answer_b": " Ness",
        "answer_c": " Yoshi",
        "answer_d": " Young Link"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the game Luigis Mansion, which of these in not one of Marios lost items?",
        "correct_answer": " Marios belt",
        "answer_a": " Marios shoe",
        "answer_b": " Marios hat",
        "answer_c": " Marios belt",
        "answer_d": " Marios star"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the boss at the end of world 5 in the game Super Mario 2?",
        "correct_answer": " Clawgrip",
        "answer_a": " Birdo",
        "answer_b": " Tryclide",
        "answer_c": " Bowser",
        "answer_d": " Clawgrip"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the game Super Mario 1, which level in world 7 is a water level?",
        "correct_answer": " 7-2",
        "answer_a": " 7-1",
        "answer_b": " 7-2",
        "answer_c": " 7-4",
        "answer_d": " 7-3"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Super Mario World, you start the game on which island?",
        "correct_answer": " Yoshis Island",
        "answer_a": " Toads Island",
        "answer_b": " Yoshis Island",
        "answer_c": " Peachs Island",
        "answer_d": " Bowsers Island"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is not a playable character in the video game Mario Party 4?",
        "correct_answer": " Toad",
        "answer_a": " Peach",
        "answer_b": " Donkey Kong",
        "answer_c": " Mario",
        "answer_d": " Toad"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the game Super Mario Sunshine, where is Bowser when you fight him at the end?",
        "correct_answer": " in a hot tub",
        "answer_a": " in his castle",
        "answer_b": " in a volcano",
        "answer_c": " in a hot tub",
        "answer_d": " in the windmill with Petey Piranha"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does Mario use for his power shot in the game Mario Power Tennis?",
        "correct_answer": " a hammer",
        "answer_a": " a fiery racket",
        "answer_b": " a hammer",
        "answer_c": " a star",
        "answer_d": " a fire fist"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the God Pokemon called in Pokemon Pearl and Diamond?",
        "correct_answer": " Arceus",
        "answer_a": " Giratina",
        "answer_b": " Dialga",
        "answer_c": " Cresselia",
        "answer_d": " Arceus"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Pokemon creature Snorunt can evolve in which of the following?",
        "correct_answer": " Glalie  Froslass",
        "answer_a": " Glalie  Snolie",
        "answer_b": " Glalie  Froslass",
        "answer_c": " Glalie  Galrunt",
        "answer_d": " Glalie  Probopass"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what Pokemon version can Palkia be obtained?",
        "correct_answer": " Pearl",
        "answer_a": " Pearl",
        "answer_b": " Blue",
        "answer_c": " Diamond",
        "answer_d": " Red"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the first ever ghost Pokemon to appear in a Pokemon episiode?",
        "correct_answer": " Gengar",
        "answer_a": " Misdreavus",
        "answer_b": " Gengar",
        "answer_c": " Ghastly",
        "answer_d": " Haunter"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Pokemon abducted Professor Spencer Haled in the movie Pokemon 3?",
        "correct_answer": " Unknown",
        "answer_a": " Aipom",
        "answer_b": " Gengar",
        "answer_c": " Unknown",
        "answer_d": " Entei"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many heroes are alive at the end of Startcraft: Brood War?",
        "correct_answer": " 6 - Artanis, Arcturus Mengsk, Jim Raynor, Zeratul, Samir Duran, Sarah Kerrigan",
        "answer_a": " 6 - Artanis, Arcturus Mengsk, Jim Raynor, Zeratul, Samir Duran, Sarah Kerrigan",
        "answer_b": " 7 - Aratnis, Arcturus Mengsk, Aldaris, Samir Duran, Sarah Kerrigan, Fenix, Zeratul",
        "answer_c": " 5 - Fenix, Arcturus Mengsk, Edmund Duke, Samir Duran, Sarah Kerrigan",
        "answer_d": " 7 - Aratnis, Arcturus Mengsk, Aldaris, Samir Duran, Sarah Kerrigan, Fenix, Jim Raynor"
    },
    {
        "question": "Edmund Duke leads which group of elite fighters?",
        "correct_answer": " Alpha Squadron",
        "answer_a": " Alpha Squadron",
        "answer_b": " Beta Squadron",
        "answer_c": " Delta Squadron",
        "answer_d": " Omega Squadron"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of unit is Zeratul?",
        "correct_answer": " Dark Templar",
        "answer_a": " Dark Archon",
        "answer_b": " High Templar",
        "answer_c": " Dark Templar",
        "answer_d": " Zealot"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are characteristics of the Archon unit?",
        "correct_answer": " 10 hit points and 350 plasma shield",
        "answer_a": " 10 hit points and 250 plasma shield",
        "answer_b": " 20 hit points and 250 plasma shield",
        "answer_c": " 10 hit points and 350 plasma shield",
        "answer_d": " 20 hit points and 300 plasma shield"
    },
    {
        "question": "What unit says that in the game?",
        "correct_answer": " Dark Templar",
        "answer_a": " Zealot",
        "answer_b": " Scout",
        "answer_c": " Dark Templar",
        "answer_d": " Zealot"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Alexei Stukovs rank?",
        "correct_answer": " Vice Admiral",
        "answer_a": " General",
        "answer_b": " Admiral",
        "answer_c": " Vice Admiral",
        "answer_d": " Corporal"
    },
    {
        "question": "During which mission do Edmund Duke and Fenix die?",
        "correct_answer": " True colors",
        "answer_a": " True colors",
        "answer_b": " Omega station",
        "answer_c": " Day of lightning",
        "answer_d": " Hammer falls"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who leads the UED (United Earth Directorate forces)?",
        "correct_answer": " Gerard DuGalle",
        "answer_a": " Samir Duran",
        "answer_b": " Gerard DuGalle",
        "answer_c": " Jim Raynor",
        "answer_d": " Alexei Stukov"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Kerrigan talking to?",
        "correct_answer": " Fenix",
        "answer_a": " Zeratul",
        "answer_b": " Edmund Duke",
        "answer_c": " Fenix",
        "answer_d": " Artanis"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the Italian plumber, thats also the mascot of Nintendo?",
        "correct_answer": " Mario",
        "answer_a": " Luigi",
        "answer_b": " Donkey Kong",
        "answer_c": " Sonic",
        "answer_d": " Mario"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does KOTOR stand for?",
        "correct_answer": " Knights of the Old Republic",
        "answer_a": " Kings Of The Old Realm",
        "answer_b": " Know One Tells Our Ruses",
        "answer_c": " Kin Of Time Or Rain",
        "answer_d": " Knights of the Old Republic"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the video game Rock Band you can play multiple instruments in the band.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Age of Empires game expansion pack allows you to play as Native Americans?",
        "correct_answer": " The War Chiefs",
        "answer_a": " The War Chiefs",
        "answer_b": " The Tribal Warriors",
        "answer_c": " The Lakota Warriors",
        "answer_d": " Asian Dynasty"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Donkey Kongs tiny sidekick?",
        "correct_answer": " Diddy Kong",
        "answer_a": " Tiny Kong",
        "answer_b": " Donkey Kong Jr.",
        "answer_c": " Diddy Kong",
        "answer_d": " Mini Donkey Kong"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which GTA game features Tommy Vercetti?",
        "correct_answer": " Vice City",
        "answer_a": " Grand Theft Auto III",
        "answer_b": " San Andreas",
        "answer_c": " GTA 9,000",
        "answer_d": " Vice City"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which game is Luis Sera featured in?",
        "correct_answer": " Resident Evil 4",
        "answer_a": " Burnout Revenge",
        "answer_b": " Dead Rising",
        "answer_c": " Resident Evil 4",
        "answer_d": " Midnight Mayhem"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these games is not based on a comic book?",
        "correct_answer": " Kingdom Hearts",
        "answer_a": " The Darkness",
        "answer_b": " Ghost Rider",
        "answer_c": " Kingdom Hearts",
        "answer_d": " X-Men The Game"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these songs is not in Guitar Hero 2?",
        "correct_answer": " We Will Rock You",
        "answer_a": " Carry on My Wayward Son",
        "answer_b": " Strutter",
        "answer_c": " War Pigs",
        "answer_d": " We Will Rock You"
    },
    {
        "question": "In 2007, this game was named by IGN the 3rd best GameCube game of all time.",
        "correct_answer": " Super Smash Bros Melee",
        "answer_a": " Pikmin",
        "answer_b": " Super Smash Bros Melee",
        "answer_c": " Resident Evil 4",
        "answer_d": " Nicktoons Unite"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Legend of Zelda: Twilight Princess, what is the name of the first sword you get?",
        "correct_answer": " Wooden sword",
        "answer_a": " Ordon sword",
        "answer_b": " Four sword",
        "answer_c": " Wooden sword",
        "answer_d": " Master sword"
    },
    {
        "question": "In The Legend of Zelda: Majoras Mask, how many days do you have until the moon crashes down on Temina?",
        "correct_answer": " three",
        "answer_a": " one",
        "answer_b": " nine",
        "answer_c": " three",
        "answer_d": " six"
    },
    {
        "question": "There is at least one game of the Zelda series of games, released from 1986 to 2006, in which Zelda and Link get married.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the owner of lon-lon ranch in the Zelda series of games?",
        "correct_answer": " Talon",
        "answer_a": " Zelda",
        "answer_b": " Ingo",
        "answer_c": " Minda",
        "answer_d": " Talon"
    },
    {
        "question": "In The Legend of Zelda: Twilight Princess, what was the name of the villain that had been fired from a joker at Hyrule Castle?",
        "correct_answer": " None of these",
        "answer_a": " None of these",
        "answer_b": " Gannondorf",
        "answer_c": " Navi",
        "answer_d": " Vati"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Zelda series of games, what is the name of the tribe Gannondorf comes from?",
        "correct_answer": " Gerudo",
        "answer_a": " Zora",
        "answer_b": " Gerudo",
        "answer_c": " Goron",
        "answer_d": " Hylian"
    },
    {
        "question": "Link, one of the main characters in the Zelda series of games, is a member of what race?",
        "correct_answer": " Hylians",
        "answer_a": " Hylians",
        "answer_b": " Kokiri",
        "answer_c": " Zora",
        "answer_d": " Goron"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Links fathers name according to the Zelda series of games?",
        "correct_answer": " It has never been revealed.",
        "answer_a": " It has never been revealed.",
        "answer_b": " Gerald",
        "answer_c": " Sam",
        "answer_d": " Lance"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which Zelda game does Link turn into a bunny when he goes into the dark world without a pearl?",
        "correct_answer": " Link to the Past",
        "answer_a": " Twilight Princess",
        "answer_b": " Link to the Past",
        "answer_c": " Ocarina of Time",
        "answer_d": " Links Awakening"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which computer game is this soundtrack from?",
        "correct_answer": " Double Dragon",
        "answer_a": " Double Dragon",
        "answer_b": " Final Fight",
        "answer_c": " Punisher",
        "answer_d": " Street Fighter"
    },
    {
        "question": "What island do you start on in the online role-playing game RuneScape?",
        "correct_answer": " Tutorial Island",
        "answer_a": " Beginners Island",
        "answer_b": " Noobonia Island",
        "answer_c": " Startagonia Island",
        "answer_d": " Tutorial Island"
    },
    {
        "question": "What icon is used to start a low detail RuneScape game?",
        "correct_answer": " A warrior",
        "answer_a": " A skeleton",
        "answer_b": " An imp",
        "answer_c": " A warrior",
        "answer_d": " A barbarian"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the sword used to defeat the demon in the demon slayer quest of the online role-playing game RuneScape?",
        "correct_answer": " Silverlight",
        "answer_a": " Brightheart",
        "answer_b": " Demonbane",
        "answer_c": " The Shining Light",
        "answer_d": " Silverlight"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the online role-playing game RuneScape, what kind of fruit is grown in Karajama?",
        "correct_answer": " Bananas",
        "answer_a": " Apples",
        "answer_b": " Bananas",
        "answer_c": " Oranges",
        "answer_d": " Pineapples"
    },
    {
        "question": "Priest robes raise your mage level in the mass online game RuneScape.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the highest weapon type available to nonmembers in the online role-playing game RuneScape?",
        "correct_answer": " Rune",
        "answer_a": " Dragon",
        "answer_b": " Granite",
        "answer_c": " Rune",
        "answer_d": " Adamantite"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the fantasy realm in which the RuneScape game is set?",
        "correct_answer": " Gielinor",
        "answer_a": " None of these",
        "answer_b": " Modor",
        "answer_c": " Gomor",
        "answer_d": " Gielinor"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does Traiborn call you in the online role-playing game RuneScape?",
        "correct_answer": " Thingummywut",
        "answer_a": " Bungdungydingdong",
        "answer_b": " Hugmugabugger",
        "answer_c": " Thingummywut",
        "answer_d": " Trindindlekindy"
    },
    {
        "question": "The action in the survival horror game Resident Evil 4 takes place in what country?",
        "correct_answer": " Spain",
        "answer_a": " Germany",
        "answer_b": " Spain",
        "answer_c": " France",
        "answer_d": " USA"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the guns listed is available before you beat the Resident Evil 4 game?",
        "correct_answer": " Killer7",
        "answer_a": " Chicago typewriter",
        "answer_b": " Killer7",
        "answer_c": " Handcannon",
        "answer_d": " Infinite Launcher"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the merchants real name in the video game Resident Evil 4?",
        "correct_answer": " It is not mentioned",
        "answer_a": " Jeremy",
        "answer_b": " Krauser",
        "answer_c": " It is not mentioned",
        "answer_d": " Robert"
    },
    {
        "question": "This creature from the game Resident Evil 4 was created by splicing genes from reptiles, insects and a human into one organism.",
        "correct_answer": " U3",
        "answer_a": " None of the above",
        "answer_b": " Verdugo",
        "answer_c": " Garrador",
        "answer_d": " U3"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the survival video game Resident Evil 4, the handcannon with its exclusive upgrade does 99.9 damage and has infinite ammo.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Not including the rocket launcher, what is the second most powerful weapon in Resident Evil 4, according to its damage per shot?",
        "correct_answer": " Broken butterfly",
        "answer_a": " Semi-auto rifle",
        "answer_b": " Chicago typewriter",
        "answer_c": " Killer7",
        "answer_d": " Broken butterfly"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whose final speech ends in We shall win through no matter the cost!",
        "correct_answer": " Arcturus Mengsk",
        "answer_a": " Alexei Stukov",
        "answer_b": " Edmund Duke",
        "answer_c": " Jim Raynor",
        "answer_d": " Arcturus Mengsk"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who kills the Matriarch?",
        "correct_answer": " Zeratul",
        "answer_a": " Zeratul",
        "answer_b": " Sarah Kerrigan",
        "answer_c": " Aldaris",
        "answer_d": " Samir Duran"
    },
    {
        "question": "The words Doom to all who threaten the homeworld belong to which unit?",
        "correct_answer": " Zealot",
        "answer_a": " Zealot",
        "answer_b": " Dark Templar",
        "answer_c": " Archon",
        "answer_d": " Dark Archon"
    },
    {
        "question": "What were the words of Sarah Kerrigan to Jim Raynor when they first met?",
        "correct_answer": " You pig!",
        "answer_a": " You pig!",
        "answer_b": " Hello, Jimmy",
        "answer_c": " Hello, sheriff",
        "answer_d": " Hello, marshal"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many hit points does the Arclite Siege Tank have?",
        "correct_answer": " 150",
        "answer_a": " 140",
        "answer_b": " 160",
        "answer_c": " 150",
        "answer_d": " 120"
    },
    {
        "question": "Listen to the dialogue and determine what name is missing at the end",
        "correct_answer": " Alexei",
        "answer_a": " Raynor",
        "answer_b": " Alexei",
        "answer_c": " Gerard",
        "answer_d": " Kerrigan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What hero do these words belong to: I fear no death, I fear no enemy, our",
        "correct_answer": " Fenix",
        "answer_a": " Artanis",
        "answer_b": " Zeratul",
        "answer_c": " Fenix",
        "answer_d": " Tessadar"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the official version for the death of Alexei Stukov?",
        "correct_answer": " He dies during the final assault on planet Char",
        "answer_a": " He commits suicide after his fleet is destroyed",
        "answer_b": " He is killed by Samir Duran, because he was a traitor",
        "answer_c": " His spaceship is blown up by Prottos forces",
        "answer_d": " He dies during the final assault on planet Char"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which unit says You called down the Thunder, now reap the Whirlwind.",
        "correct_answer": " Ghost",
        "answer_a": " Ghost",
        "answer_b": " Medic",
        "answer_c": " Marine",
        "answer_d": " Firebat"
    },
    {
        "question": "This sound clip is from what classic Nintendo game?",
        "correct_answer": " Super Mario Bros",
        "answer_a": " Star Fox",
        "answer_b": " Donkey Kong",
        "answer_c": " Super Mario Bros",
        "answer_d": " The Legend of Zelda"
    },
    {
        "question": "This sound clip is from what NES game featuring a creature that could eat anything?",
        "correct_answer": " Kirbys Adventure",
        "answer_a": " Metroid",
        "answer_b": " Legend of Zelda",
        "answer_c": " Super Mario Bros.",
        "answer_d": " Kirbys Adventure"
    },
    {
        "question": "This is the theme to what Xbox video game?",
        "correct_answer": " Halo",
        "answer_a": " Final Fantasy",
        "answer_b": " Eldar Scrolls IV: Oblivion",
        "answer_c": " Rainbow 6",
        "answer_d": " Halo"
    },
    {
        "question": "This is the overworld theme to this NES game that introduced the save function because the game took so long to complete.",
        "correct_answer": " Legend of Zelda",
        "answer_a": " Metroid",
        "answer_b": " Donkey Kong",
        "answer_c": " Legend of Zelda",
        "answer_d": " Super Mario Bros."
    },
    {
        "question": "This is the victory theme to what popular video game series?",
        "correct_answer": " Final Fantasy",
        "answer_a": " Mortal Combat",
        "answer_b": " Legend of Zelda",
        "answer_c": " Final Fantasy",
        "answer_d": " Super Mario"
    },
    {
        "question": "From which fighting game is this sound clip?",
        "correct_answer": " Super Smash Bros. Melee",
        "answer_a": " Street Fighter II",
        "answer_b": " Super Smash Bros. Melee",
        "answer_c": " Teken 4",
        "answer_d": " Soul Caliber II"
    },
    {
        "question": "This sound clip is from what Game Boy game that spawned an anime TV show and a collectible card game?",
        "correct_answer": " Pokemon",
        "answer_a": " Final Fantasy",
        "answer_b": " Pokemon",
        "answer_c": " Magic the Gathering",
        "answer_d": " Yu-Gi-Oh"
    },
    {
        "question": "This sound clip is from what PC RTS game?",
        "correct_answer": " Age of Empires II",
        "answer_a": " Age of Empires II",
        "answer_b": " StarCraft",
        "answer_c": " Command and Conquer",
        "answer_d": " Warcraft III"
    },
    {
        "question": "This sound clip is a theme in which of the following Legend of Zelda games?",
        "correct_answer": " The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time",
        "answer_a": " The Legend of Zelda: A Link to the Past",
        "answer_b": " The Legend of Zelda",
        "answer_c": " The Legend of Zelda: The Wind Waker",
        "answer_d": " The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time"
    },
    {
        "question": "This sound clip is from what video game series?",
        "correct_answer": " Star Fox",
        "answer_a": " Star Wars: Rouge Squadron",
        "answer_b": " Final Fantasy",
        "answer_c": " Star Fox",
        "answer_d": " Halo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these levels is on both Star Wars: Battlefront 1 and 2?",
        "correct_answer": " Kamino",
        "answer_a": " Death Star",
        "answer_b": " Kamino",
        "answer_c": " Bespin",
        "answer_d": " Mustafar"
    },
    {
        "question": "You can control Jedi on both Star Wars: Battlefront 1 and 2.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the default number of points to destroy a ship in a space battle on Star Wars: Battlefront  2?",
        "correct_answer": " 180",
        "answer_a": " 500",
        "answer_b": " 200",
        "answer_c": " 10",
        "answer_d": " 180"
    },
    {
        "question": "Choose the correct order for player points bonuses in Star Wars: Battlefront from least to greatest.",
        "correct_answer": " Endurance, Guardian, War Hero",
        "answer_a": " Endurance, Guardian, War Hero",
        "answer_b": " Guardian, Endurance, War Hero",
        "answer_c": " War Hero, Guardian, Endurance",
        "answer_d": " Marksman, Demolition, Technician"
    },
    {
        "question": "The two levels on Kashyyyk on Star Wars: Battlefront 1 are Islands and Docks.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "On the Star Wars: Battlefront game, which of these is among the non-player characters of the game?",
        "correct_answer": " Jawas",
        "answer_a": " Mace Windu",
        "answer_b": " Heavy weapons soldier",
        "answer_c": " Luke Skywalker",
        "answer_d": " Jawas"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who controls the AT-ATs on Hoth in Star Wars: Battlefront?",
        "correct_answer": " Empire",
        "answer_a": " Empire",
        "answer_b": " Rebels",
        "answer_c": " Republic",
        "answer_d": " CIS"
    },
    {
        "question": "Warchief Thrall is the leader of which clan?",
        "correct_answer": " Doomhammer",
        "answer_a": " Warsong",
        "answer_b": " Death Spear",
        "answer_c": " Black Rock",
        "answer_d": " Doomhammer"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of creature is the DeathWing?",
        "correct_answer": " Black Dragon",
        "answer_a": " Black Dragon",
        "answer_b": " Red Dragon",
        "answer_c": " Bone Dragon",
        "answer_d": " Green Dragon"
    },
    {
        "question": "What unit or hero does the phrase Speak up fool belong to?",
        "correct_answer": " Prince Arthas as Dead Knight",
        "answer_a": " Ghoul",
        "answer_b": " Druid of the Claw",
        "answer_c": " Prince Arthas as Dead Knight",
        "answer_d": " Prince Arthas"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who kills Mannoroth?",
        "correct_answer": " Grom Hellscream",
        "answer_a": " Thrall",
        "answer_b": " Prince Arthas",
        "answer_c": " Grom Hellscream",
        "answer_d": " Illidan Stormrage"
    },
    {
        "question": "What unit or hero does this phrase belong to?",
        "correct_answer": " Dwarf Rifleman",
        "answer_a": " muradin bronzebeard",
        "answer_b": " Human Footman",
        "answer_c": " Dwarf Rifleman",
        "answer_d": " Throll Hunter"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which building makes the Druid of the Claw unit?",
        "correct_answer": " Ancient of  Lore",
        "answer_a": " Ancient of  Lore",
        "answer_b": " Ancient of  Wind",
        "answer_c": " Ancient of Wisdom",
        "answer_d": " Ancient of War"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who rides \u201cNightsabre Panthers\u201d?",
        "correct_answer": " Huntresses",
        "answer_a": " Wind Druids",
        "answer_b": " Head Hunters",
        "answer_c": " Huntresses",
        "answer_d": " Archers"
    },
    {
        "question": "What unit or hero does the phrase \u201cI can see clearly, now the rain has gone\u201d belong to?",
        "correct_answer": " Grom Hellscream",
        "answer_a": " Thrall",
        "answer_b": " Shadow Hunter",
        "answer_c": " Grom Hellscream",
        "answer_d": " Thief"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Pokemon TV series, Ash saw a Gyarados in the first episode.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "On what other character is Ash Ketchum loosely based in the Pokemon video games?",
        "correct_answer": " Red",
        "answer_a": " Blue",
        "answer_b": " Yellow",
        "answer_c": " Green",
        "answer_d": " Red"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is the Pokemon character Raikou included in any of the first ten Pokemon movies?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first season of Johto called in Pokemon series?",
        "correct_answer": " Johto Journeys",
        "answer_a": " Johto",
        "answer_b": " Johto Quest",
        "answer_c": " Johto Journeys",
        "answer_d": " Master Quest"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was the tenth Pokemon movie released simultaneously in Japan and the USA?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can you find the gym leader Blaine in the video games Pokemon Gold and Silver and Pokemon Crystal?",
        "correct_answer": " Seaform Islands",
        "answer_a": " Celadon City",
        "answer_b": " Seaform Islands",
        "answer_c": " Cinnabar Island",
        "answer_d": " Fusia city"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the very first car you drive in the Need for Speed: Most Wanted game?",
        "correct_answer": " BMW M3 GTR",
        "answer_a": " Golf GTI",
        "answer_b": " BMW M3 GTR",
        "answer_c": " Corvette C6",
        "answer_d": " Lamborghini Gallardo"
    },
    {
        "question": "There are a total of 20 blacklist drivers in the game Need for Speed: Most Wanted.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the racing game Need for Speed: Most Wanted, what are the street names of  Blacklist numbers 1, 4, 7, and 15?",
        "correct_answer": " Razor, JV, Kaze, Sonny",
        "answer_a": " Razor, JV, Kaze, Sonny",
        "answer_b": " Taz, Big Lou, Baron, Ronnie",
        "answer_c": " Kaze, Big Lou, Bull, Razor",
        "answer_d": " Webster, Vic, Izzy, Bull"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many maximum infractions can you get in a single pursuit in the game Need for Speed: Most Wanted?",
        "correct_answer": " 8",
        "answer_a": " 10",
        "answer_b": " 9",
        "answer_c": " 8",
        "answer_d": " 7"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you have a rap sheet in the game Need for Speed: Most Wanted?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following refers to the ability to win a Blacklist opponents car in the game Need for Speed: Most Wanted?",
        "correct_answer": " pink slip",
        "answer_a": " pink slip",
        "answer_b": " gold bars",
        "answer_c": " orange tye",
        "answer_d": " thong wrap"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the racing game Need for Speed: Most Wanted, where is is Blacklist number one located?",
        "correct_answer": " Rockport",
        "answer_a": " Johan City",
        "answer_b": " Rockport",
        "answer_c": " Goodwales",
        "answer_d": " Amberhill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who created the theme song of the Super Mario Brothers game?",
        "correct_answer": " Koji Kondo",
        "answer_a": " Nobuo Uematsu",
        "answer_b": " Koji Kondo",
        "answer_c": " Yasunori Mitsuda",
        "answer_d": " Shigeru Miyamoto"
    },
    {
        "question": "Shigeru Miyamoto constructed the arcade game Donkey Kongs music himself, using an Electronic Keyboard.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "The core of this gaming console, released in 1977, was combined with a display and sound chip known as the TIA, for Television Interface Adaptor.  The console was capable of producing 2 channel mono sound.",
        "correct_answer": " Atari 2600",
        "answer_a": " Sega Master System",
        "answer_b": " Intellivision",
        "answer_c": " Atari 2600",
        "answer_d": " Nintendo Entertainment System (NES)"
    },
    {
        "question": "The sound chip of the Commodore 64 home computer, released in 1982, was very advanced for its time.  It had three channels with several different waveforms, which could reach 8 different octaves each (approximately 16 - 4000 Hz).  Name the chip.",
        "correct_answer": " Sound Interface Device",
        "answer_a": " Sound Interface Disk",
        "answer_b": " Sound Interface Component",
        "answer_c": " Sound Interface Device",
        "answer_d": " Sound Interface Chip"
    },
    {
        "question": "My rogue in the game Dungeons and Dragons wants to use a wand of Greater Invisibility. In order to do this he must make a Use Magic Device check at what Difficulty Class?",
        "correct_answer": " 20",
        "answer_a": " 25",
        "answer_b": " 30",
        "answer_c": " 20",
        "answer_d": " 15"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the listed bonuses in the game Dungeons and Dragons stacks?",
        "correct_answer": " Dodge",
        "answer_a": " Dodge",
        "answer_b": " Enchantment",
        "answer_c": " Armor",
        "answer_d": " Divine"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these feats does not prevent attacks of opportunity in one form or another in the role-playing game Dungeons and Dragons?",
        "correct_answer": " Flyby Attack",
        "answer_a": " Spring Attack",
        "answer_b": " Flyby Attack",
        "answer_c": " Improved Unarmed Strike",
        "answer_d": " Improved Trip"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Knowledge Skill would allow you to determine the type of Giant you are facing in Dungeons and Dragons?",
        "correct_answer": " Nature",
        "answer_a": " Dungeoneering",
        "answer_b": " Religion",
        "answer_c": " Arcane",
        "answer_d": " Nature"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the game Dungeons and Dragons, a character with 5 ranks in Bluff gains a +2 synergy bonus to all these skills but one. Which is the odd one?",
        "correct_answer": " Gather Information",
        "answer_a": " Diplomacy",
        "answer_b": " Intimidate",
        "answer_c": " Sleight of Hand",
        "answer_d": " Gather Information"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is not a correct entrance requirement to join the Assassin Prestige Class in Dungeons and Dragons?",
        "correct_answer": " Disguise 8 ranks",
        "answer_a": " Disguise 8 ranks",
        "answer_b": " Move Silently 8 ranks",
        "answer_c": " Hide 8 ranks",
        "answer_d": " Alignment: Any evil"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the game Dungeons and Dragons, Aamonks Ki Strike ability evolves in what order?",
        "correct_answer": " Magic, Lawful, Adamantine",
        "answer_a": " Magic, Adamantine, Lawful",
        "answer_b": " Lawful, Magic, Adamantine",
        "answer_c": " Magic, Lawful, Adamantine",
        "answer_d": " Adamantine, Magic, Lawful"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Dungeons and Dragons, the Tumble Difficulty Class needed to kip up, according the Complete Adventurer book, is what?",
        "correct_answer": " 35",
        "answer_a": " 30",
        "answer_b": " 35",
        "answer_c": " 40",
        "answer_d": " 25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which class in Dungeons and Dragons does not get evasion?",
        "correct_answer": " Barbarian",
        "answer_a": " Monk",
        "answer_b": " Rogue",
        "answer_c": " Ranger",
        "answer_d": " Barbarian"
    },
    {
        "question": "Of the choices for a Rangers favored enemy in Dungeons and Dragons, which number is immune to sneak attacks?",
        "correct_answer": " 5",
        "answer_a": " 6",
        "answer_b": " 4",
        "answer_c": " 3",
        "answer_d": " 5"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many golden skulltulas could you get as child Link out of the whole game The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time?",
        "correct_answer": " 35",
        "answer_a": " 35",
        "answer_b": " 10",
        "answer_c": " 20",
        "answer_d": " 30"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many heart pieces can you get as adult Link in the game The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time?",
        "correct_answer": " 24",
        "answer_a": " 5",
        "answer_b": " 24",
        "answer_c": " 20",
        "answer_d": " 10"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the video game The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time, what are the two places where you can get the hylian shield?",
        "correct_answer": " Kakariko Graveyard and Hyrule town market.",
        "answer_a": " lake Hylia and Hyrule castle.",
        "answer_b": " Haunted Wasteland and Zoras domain.",
        "answer_c": " Goron city and Kokiri forest.",
        "answer_d": " Kakariko Graveyard and Hyrule town market."
    },
    {
        "question": "In The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time, how many items do you get that are improved later in the game?",
        "correct_answer": " four",
        "answer_a": " one",
        "answer_b": " six",
        "answer_c": " three",
        "answer_d": " four"
    },
    {
        "question": "In The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time, how many items do you trade to get the Biggorons sword?",
        "correct_answer": " 9",
        "answer_a": " 11",
        "answer_b": " 7",
        "answer_c": " 10",
        "answer_d": " 9"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the video game The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time, Link wore tunics in three colors. They were green, red and yellow.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many hidden fairy fountains are there in the game The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time, not counting the great fairies?",
        "correct_answer": " 6",
        "answer_a": " 3",
        "answer_b": " 5",
        "answer_c": " 6",
        "answer_d": " 2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a character class in World of Warcraft?",
        "correct_answer": " Blood-Elf",
        "answer_a": " Warlock",
        "answer_b": " Paladin",
        "answer_c": " Blood-Elf",
        "answer_d": " Druid"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following races cannot play a Hunter in World of Warcraft?",
        "correct_answer": " Gnome",
        "answer_a": " Draenei",
        "answer_b": " Gnome",
        "answer_c": " Dwarf",
        "answer_d": " Tauren"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Horde and the Alliance are the two playable factions in World of Warcraft.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In World of Warcraft, it is possible to fly from Theramore to Stormwind.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In World of Warcraft, it is sometimes necessary to fight other groups of players inside an instance.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a realm type in World of Warcraft?",
        "correct_answer": " RP",
        "answer_a": " PvP",
        "answer_b": " RP",
        "answer_c": " RP-PvP",
        "answer_d": " Normal"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the Iron Maiden song performed in Guitar Hero 3?",
        "correct_answer": " The Number of the Beast",
        "answer_a": " The Metal",
        "answer_b": " Enter Sandman",
        "answer_c": " One",
        "answer_d": " The Number of the Beast"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who sings Slow Ride, one of the songs included in Guitar Hero 3?",
        "correct_answer": " Foghat",
        "answer_a": " Foghat",
        "answer_b": " Metallica",
        "answer_c": " ZZ Top",
        "answer_d": " Sonic Youth"
    },
    {
        "question": "What song by Tenacious D appeared in the video game Guitar Hero 3?",
        "correct_answer": " The Metal",
        "answer_a": " Lou",
        "answer_b": " Bulls On Parade",
        "answer_c": " Anarchy in the U.K.",
        "answer_d": " The Metal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tom Morello is a member of the band Sonic Youth.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first place you get a gig at on Guitar Hero 3?",
        "correct_answer": " Backyard Bash",
        "answer_a": " Fenway Park",
        "answer_b": " Backyard Bash",
        "answer_c": " Yankee Stadium",
        "answer_d": " Mitchs Moose Lounge"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the way to evolve the pokemon Tangela to tangrowth in the Diamond and Pearl Pokemon series?",
        "correct_answer": " Level it up after learning ancient power.",
        "answer_a": " Level it up after learning ancient power.",
        "answer_b": " Trade it while holding a growth incense.",
        "answer_c": " Use a leaf stone on it.",
        "answer_d": " Level it up."
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you evolve Rhydon into Rhyperior in the Diamond and Pearl Pokemon series?",
        "correct_answer": " Trade Rhydon up while holding a protector.",
        "answer_a": " Level Rhydon up.",
        "answer_b": " Trade Rhydon up while holding a hard stone.",
        "answer_c": " Trade Rhydon up while holding a protector.",
        "answer_d": " Trade Rhydon."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what way can you evolve the pokemon Gilgar into Gliscor in the Diamond and Pearl Pokemon series for Nintendo DS?",
        "correct_answer": " None of these",
        "answer_a": " Trade it.",
        "answer_b": " Trade it holding a razor fang.",
        "answer_c": " None of these",
        "answer_d": " Level up."
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you evolve an Electabuzz into an Electrivire in the Diamond and Pearl Pokemon series?",
        "correct_answer": " Trade it while holding a electrizer.",
        "answer_a": " None of these",
        "answer_b": " Trade it while holding a electrizer.",
        "answer_c": " Give it a electrizer.",
        "answer_d": " Train it while holding a electrizer."
    },
    {
        "question": "In Pokemon Diamond and Pearl, in what way do you evolve a Porygon2 into a Porygon-Z?",
        "correct_answer": " Give it a dubious disc and trade it.",
        "answer_a": " Give it an upgrade and trade it.",
        "answer_b": " Give it a tech disc and trade it.",
        "answer_c": " Level it up.",
        "answer_d": " Give it a dubious disc and trade it."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the way to evolve a Yanma into a Yanmega in the Diamond and Pearl Pokemon series for Nintendo DS?",
        "correct_answer": " At level 33 let Yanma learn anchient power.",
        "answer_a": " At level 33 let Yanma learn rollout.",
        "answer_b": " At level 33 let Yanma learn silver wind.",
        "answer_c": " None of these",
        "answer_d": " At level 33 let Yanma learn anchient power."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is the correct way to evolve a Kirlia into a Gallade in Pokemon Diamond and Pearl?",
        "correct_answer": " None of these",
        "answer_a": " Use a dawn stone on Kirlia.",
        "answer_b": " Trade Kirlia.",
        "answer_c": " Use a dawn stone on a female Kirlia.",
        "answer_d": " None of these"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what way can you evolve the pokemon Snorunt into a Frosslass in the Diamond and Pearl Pokemon series for Nintendo DS?",
        "correct_answer": " Use a dawn stone on a female Snorunt.",
        "answer_a": " Use a dawn stone on a male Snorunt.",
        "answer_b": " Use a shiny stone on a male Snorunt.",
        "answer_c": " Use a dawn stone on a female Snorunt.",
        "answer_d": " Use a shiny stone on a females Snorunt."
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you evolve a Dusclops into a Duskinoir in Pokemon Diamond and Pearl?",
        "correct_answer": " Trade a Dusclops that is holding a reapers cloth.",
        "answer_a": " Trade a Dusclops.",
        "answer_b": " Train Dusclops at night.",
        "answer_c": " Trade a Dusclops that is holding a reapers cloth.",
        "answer_d": " None of these"
    },
    {
        "question": "At what location does the PS2 role-playing game Final Fantasy X start?",
        "correct_answer": " Zanarkand",
        "answer_a": " Zanarkand",
        "answer_b": " Mt. Gagazet",
        "answer_c": " Besaid",
        "answer_d": " Kilika"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which other team member do you meet first in the PS2 game Final Fantasy X?",
        "correct_answer": " Auron",
        "answer_a": " Rikku",
        "answer_b": " Kimhari",
        "answer_c": " Auron",
        "answer_d": " Yuna"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Final Fantasy X, where does Yuna perform her first Sending?",
        "correct_answer": " Kilika",
        "answer_a": " Kilika",
        "answer_b": " Besaid",
        "answer_c": " Djos\u00c3\u00a9",
        "answer_d": " Home"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Final Fantasy X, when you enter the Farplane in Guadosalam to talk to Yunas father, Auron stays behind because he is scared of confronting Jecht.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is not a blitzball team from the PS2 game Final Fantasy X?",
        "correct_answer": " Ronso Rovers",
        "answer_a": " Guado Glories",
        "answer_b": " Besiad Aurochs",
        "answer_c": " Ronso Rovers",
        "answer_d": " Luca Goers"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Final Fantasy X, where do you get each of the following aeons respectively: Ifrit, Shiva, Yojimbo, Valefor, Magus Sisters, Ixion?",
        "correct_answer": " Kilika, Macalania, Calm Lands, Besaid, Requiem, Djose",
        "answer_a": " Djose, Requiem, Besaid, Macalania, Calm Lands, Kilika",
        "answer_b": " Kilika, Macalania, Calm Lands, Besaid, Requiem, Djose",
        "answer_c": " Macalania, Kilika, Calm Lands, Gagazet, Requiem, Djose.",
        "answer_d": " Kilika, Djose, Calm Lands, Requiem, Besiad, Macalania"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is Maester Seymour the final time you have to fight him in the PS2 role-playing game Final Fantasy X?",
        "correct_answer": " In the Sea of Sorrows inside Sin",
        "answer_a": " On top of Mt. Gagazet",
        "answer_b": " On the Highroad in Bevelle",
        "answer_c": " Outside Besaid",
        "answer_d": " In the Sea of Sorrows inside Sin"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to Final Fantasy X, what does this sentence in the Al Bhed language translate to: Xna ehi ayo degurk e wouj?",
        "correct_answer": " Why are you taking a quiz?",
        "answer_a": " How can you ignore a call?",
        "answer_b": " Did you see Tidus swim?",
        "answer_c": " Why not see snakes a rule!",
        "answer_d": " Why are you taking a quiz?"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Yunas speech at the end of Final Fantasy X, what phrase is an almost direct reference to Tidus?",
        "correct_answer": " The dreams that have faded",
        "answer_a": " The friends who have gone",
        "answer_b": " Stand by your friends",
        "answer_c": " The dreams that have faded",
        "answer_d": " Life is a game of blitzball"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does Sarias Song do in Legend of Zelda Ocarina of Time?",
        "correct_answer": " Enables you to talk to Saria",
        "answer_a": " Enables you to fly",
        "answer_b": " Teleports you to the Hyrule Castle",
        "answer_c": " Teleports you anywhere",
        "answer_d": " Enables you to talk to Saria"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Legend of Zelda Majoras Mask you are transformed into a Zora by Ganondorf.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is it true that in Legend of Zelda Twilight Princess, after you get the Master Sword you can transform into a wolf any time you like?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is it true that in Legend of Zelda and the Wind Waker, after you beat the game you can make a new file and not get Links green clothing?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Legend of Zelda Ocarina of Time, once you pull out the Master Sword you will become older.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is it true that in the whole Legend of Zelda series, the currency is rupees?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can you find the Spiritual Gem of Water in Legend of Zelda and the Ocarina of Time?",
        "correct_answer": " Zoras Domain",
        "answer_a": " Deku Tree",
        "answer_b": " Zoras Domain",
        "answer_c": " Death Moutain",
        "answer_d": " Sky World"
    },
    {
        "question": "What game console is the strategy video game Thrillville available on?",
        "correct_answer": " Xbox/PSP/PS2",
        "answer_a": " DS/Gamecube/PS3",
        "answer_b": " Xbox/PSP/PS2",
        "answer_c": " PSP/PS3/PS2",
        "answer_d": " PS3/PS2/DS"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the strategy video game Thrillville, there are 4 categories in the park menu.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you take control of your staff members in the Thrillville video game strategy?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the simulation and strategy Thrillville, what is the best way to increase your attraction meter?",
        "correct_answer": " Play the flirt mini-game",
        "answer_a": " Play the flirt mini-game",
        "answer_b": " Talk with the person",
        "answer_c": " A challenge the person to a mini-game off",
        "answer_d": " Ride rides together"
    },
    {
        "question": "The video game Thrillville is rated T by the Entertainment Software Rating Board (ESRB).",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Thrillville strategy video game you cant make money off of mini-games.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Thrillville video game, can you make money off of playing mini-golf?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "You suck up trash by using a vacuum gun in the Thrillville video game.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who are the people that save the gang from Tabuu in Super Smash Bros. Brawl?",
        "correct_answer": " Ness, King Dedede, Luigi, Kirby",
        "answer_a": " Ness, King Dedede, Luigi, Kirby",
        "answer_b": " Mario, Luigi, Pit, Bowser",
        "answer_c": " Nobody saves them.",
        "answer_d": " R.O.B., Lucario, Snake"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many rooms are there in the Great Maze in Super Smash Bros. Brawl?",
        "correct_answer": " 40",
        "answer_a": " There is no great maze.",
        "answer_b": " 126",
        "answer_c": " 999999",
        "answer_d": " 40"
    },
    {
        "question": "What character from Super Smash Bros. Brawl was not in Super Smash Bros. Melee?",
        "correct_answer": " Ike",
        "answer_a": " Pikachu",
        "answer_b": " Falco",
        "answer_c": " Link",
        "answer_d": " Ike"
    },
    {
        "question": "Including the Melee Pokemon Stadium, how many stadiums in Super Smash Bros. Brawl are related to Pokemon?",
        "correct_answer": " 3",
        "answer_a": " 2",
        "answer_b": " 6",
        "answer_c": " 1",
        "answer_d": " 3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the function of the the Astral Amulet in the computer game Chrono Cross?",
        "correct_answer": " Serves as a key to open  dimension ports to other worlds",
        "answer_a": " Serves as a key to open  dimension ports to other worlds",
        "answer_b": " To see the future",
        "answer_c": " Makes you invisible",
        "answer_d": " Upgrades your weapons"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the computer game Chrono Cross, the water dragon gives you what ability?",
        "correct_answer": " Ice Breath",
        "answer_a": " Ice Breath",
        "answer_b": " Fire attack",
        "answer_c": " Blizzard storm",
        "answer_d": " Water attack"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who made the following statement in the game Chrono Cross: I love you so much... That is why I sometimes desire to smash you to bits!!!?",
        "correct_answer": " Fate",
        "answer_a": " Fate",
        "answer_b": " Kid",
        "answer_c": " Lynx",
        "answer_d": " Sarge"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these songs from the Chrono Cross soundtrack is on the sound clip?",
        "correct_answer": " Radical Dreamers",
        "answer_a": " Garden of the Gods",
        "answer_b": " Radical Dreamers",
        "answer_c": " Frozen Flame",
        "answer_d": " Dream of  the Shore Near Another World"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Chrono Cross character delivered the following words: In your eyes, I perceive both the look of a beauty  and the look of a beast.?",
        "correct_answer": " Fortune Teller",
        "answer_a": " Harle",
        "answer_b": " Kid",
        "answer_c": " Fortune Teller",
        "answer_d": " Serge"
    },
    {
        "question": "Listen to the sound clip and name the song from the Chrono Cross soundtrack.",
        "correct_answer": " Dreamwatch of time",
        "answer_a": " Dreamwatch of time",
        "answer_b": " Radical Dreamers",
        "answer_c": " Time Scar",
        "answer_d": " Dragon Knight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is Gyarados a water and flying type of Pokemon?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of Pokemon is Sableye?",
        "correct_answer": " Ghost dark",
        "answer_a": " Ghost",
        "answer_b": " Ghost dark",
        "answer_c": " Ghost psychic",
        "answer_d": " Ghost poison"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of Pokemon is Tyranitar?",
        "correct_answer": " Rock dark",
        "answer_a": " Rock dark",
        "answer_b": " Ground dark",
        "answer_c": " Ground",
        "answer_d": " Ground rock"
    },
    {
        "question": "Gengar is a ghost dark type of Pokemon.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is the Pokemon Togekiss flying and normal type of Pokemon?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the Pokemon Empolean belong only to the water type of Pokemon?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is Typlosion only a fire type of Pokemon?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the online game RuneScape, you can wear rune platebody without doing the quest Dragonslayer.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the game RuneScape, big bones get your prayer level up higher than dragon bones.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the RuneScape character who is the duke of Lumberidge.",
        "correct_answer": " Horacio",
        "answer_a": " Horacio",
        "answer_b": " Haracio",
        "answer_c": " Roald",
        "answer_d": " Royald"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the RuneScape game, you have to be level 85 to mine rune.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In RuneScape, green dragonhide is better than black dragonhide.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the game RuneScape, wearing Zamorack armour requires this level.",
        "correct_answer": " 40",
        "answer_a": " 50",
        "answer_b": " 40",
        "answer_c": " 35",
        "answer_d": " 99"
    },
    {
        "question": "At the start of the RPG game Final Fantasy VIII, which characters are shown in the opening movie?",
        "correct_answer": " Squall, Seifer, Rinoa, Edea",
        "answer_a": " Squall, Seifer, Rinoa, Edea",
        "answer_b": " Squall, Rinoa",
        "answer_c": " Squall, Seifer, Quistis",
        "answer_d": " Zell, Selphie, Squall"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is inside the lamp given to you by Headmaster Cid before your first official SEED mission in the role-playing game Final Fantasy VIII?",
        "correct_answer": " Diablos",
        "answer_a": " Ethers",
        "answer_b": " Ifrit",
        "answer_c": " Potions",
        "answer_d": " Diablos"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Final Fantasy VIII, what is Seifers romantic dream?",
        "correct_answer": " To be Edeas knight",
        "answer_a": " To be Edeas knight",
        "answer_b": " To marry Selphie",
        "answer_c": " To date Rinoa",
        "answer_d": " To go on holiday with Ade"
    },
    {
        "question": "Did Quistis Trepe from Final Fantasy VIII have a group of admirers called the Trepies?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did Squall say to the torturer in D-District Prison about SEED in Final Fantasy VIII?",
        "correct_answer": " They want to plant flowers and then invade the countries.",
        "answer_a": " They want to kill as many Galbadians as possible.",
        "answer_b": " They want to nuke the planet and fly to a sanctuary.",
        "answer_c": " They want to plant flowers and then invade the countries.",
        "answer_d": " They want to master as many GFs as possible."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two characters played Rock, Paper, Scissors in the role-playing game Final Fantasy VIII?",
        "correct_answer": " The Brothers",
        "answer_a": " Seifer and Squall",
        "answer_b": " Adel and Edea",
        "answer_c": " The Brothers",
        "answer_d": " Squall and Zell"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the last fight of the role-playing game Final Fantasy VIII, who does Ultimecia summon?",
        "correct_answer": " Griever",
        "answer_a": " None of these",
        "answer_b": " Rinoa",
        "answer_c": " Ultima Weapon",
        "answer_d": " Griever"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the game Animal Crossing, the players must work part-time for the character who gives them their first house.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the video game Animal Crossing the player can dig up fossils.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is not included in the game Animal Crossing?",
        "correct_answer": " A barbers shop.",
        "answer_a": " A tailors shop",
        "answer_b": " A dump",
        "answer_c": " A museum",
        "answer_d": " A barbers shop."
    },
    {
        "question": "In the game Animal Crossing your character may have horns.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you have pets in the game Animal Crossing?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you have two houses in the Nintendo game Animal Crossing?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What can you have in your house in the game Animal Crossing?",
        "correct_answer": " A basement",
        "answer_a": " Rats",
        "answer_b": " A mailbox",
        "answer_c": " A roller-coaster",
        "answer_d": " A basement"
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you own a shop in the game Animal Crossing?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "The seasons in the game Animal Crossing change as the seasons actually change in real life.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Runescape, what creature lives in the basement of Draynor Manor?",
        "correct_answer": " a vampire",
        "answer_a": " a vampire",
        "answer_b": " a witch",
        "answer_c": " a werewolf",
        "answer_d": " a zombie"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the highest level your character can go up to in the Runescape game for non-members?",
        "correct_answer": " 126",
        "answer_a": " 99",
        "answer_b": " 126",
        "answer_c": " 113",
        "answer_d": " It never ends"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Runescape, you must have level 40 defence to wear adamant armor.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What fruit grows on Karmaja in the Runescape video game?",
        "correct_answer": " bananas",
        "answer_a": " peaches",
        "answer_b": " oranges",
        "answer_c": " apples",
        "answer_d": " bananas"
    },
    {
        "question": "What item do you obtain from the 2006 Runescape Christmas Special?",
        "correct_answer": " a reindeer hat",
        "answer_a": " a pair of Santas magical boots",
        "answer_b": " a reindeer hat",
        "answer_c": " a Santa hat",
        "answer_d": " a polar bear suit"
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you kill demons in a non-members world of Runescape?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you wear goblin mail in Runescape?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Runescape, you must have a level of 99 on any skill to get a Skill Cape.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sasuke, one of the main characters in the anime series Naruto, is branded with a cursed seal.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these anime characters can use the technique, known as Rasengan?",
        "correct_answer": " Naruto",
        "answer_a": " Kakashi",
        "answer_b": " Lee",
        "answer_c": " Tenten",
        "answer_d": " Naruto"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did anime character Sasuke say when he received the cursed seal?",
        "correct_answer": " Im an avenger.",
        "answer_a": " Ill destroy your whole clan.",
        "answer_b": " Im an avenger.",
        "answer_c": " With this power Ill brake every bone in your body.",
        "answer_d": " You are dead."
    },
    {
        "question": "Fictional character Naruto killed Gaara.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Narutos favorite food?",
        "correct_answer": " ramen",
        "answer_a": " tomatoes",
        "answer_b": " pizza",
        "answer_c": " brocoli",
        "answer_d": " ramen"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who taught Sasuke the Chidori technique in the Naruto series?",
        "correct_answer": " Kakashi",
        "answer_a": " Naruto",
        "answer_b": " Itachi",
        "answer_c": " Kakashi",
        "answer_d": " Orochimaru"
    },
    {
        "question": "What technique in the Naruto series was created by Kakashi?",
        "correct_answer": " Chidori",
        "answer_a": " Primary lotus",
        "answer_b": " Rasengan",
        "answer_c": " Leaf whirlwind",
        "answer_d": " Chidori"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does Naruto dream of being in the self-titled anime series?",
        "correct_answer": " hokage",
        "answer_a": " hokage",
        "answer_b": " real estate salesman",
        "answer_c": " singer",
        "answer_d": " a pizza man"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Naruto character was initially infatuated with Sasuke?",
        "correct_answer": " Sakura",
        "answer_a": " Ino",
        "answer_b": " None of these",
        "answer_c": " Sakura",
        "answer_d": " Hinata"
    },
    {
        "question": "You get the P90 weapon at what level in Call of Duty 4?",
        "correct_answer": " 40",
        "answer_a": " 37",
        "answer_b": " 43",
        "answer_c": " 34",
        "answer_d": " 40"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many different weapons are there in Call of Duty 4?",
        "correct_answer": " 29",
        "answer_a": " 30",
        "answer_b": " 29",
        "answer_c": " 17",
        "answer_d": " 22"
    },
    {
        "question": "You can go into 15 Prestiges on XBox Livve.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Call of Duty 4 you can run around with your knife and kill as many people as you want with it.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Barret .50 Caliber is the most powerful sniper rifle in the game Call of Duty 4.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many skins for the weapons are there in Call of Duty 4?",
        "correct_answer": " 6",
        "answer_a": " 5",
        "answer_b": " 6",
        "answer_c": " 3",
        "answer_d": " 1"
    },
    {
        "question": "If you shoot a person in the head in the game Call of Duty 4, they can survive.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is not a stage in the first game of Banjo and Kazooie for Nintendo 64?",
        "correct_answer": " Cloud Cuckooland",
        "answer_a": " Gobis Valley",
        "answer_b": " Mumbos Mountain",
        "answer_c": " Cloud Cuckooland",
        "answer_d": " Freezeezy Peak"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the adventure video game Banjo-Kazooie, how many turtles are in Tiptups choir?",
        "correct_answer": " 6",
        "answer_a": " 7",
        "answer_b": " 6",
        "answer_c": " 5",
        "answer_d": " 8"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Gobis Valley from the Banjo-Kazooie adventure video game, how many notes are there in front of the door that you ride the magic carpet to?",
        "correct_answer": " 5",
        "answer_a": " 3",
        "answer_b": " 5",
        "answer_c": " 9",
        "answer_d": " 7"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Mad Monster Mansion from the Banjo-Kazooie video game, what is the time shown on the clock above the church?",
        "correct_answer": " None of these",
        "answer_a": " 13 oclock",
        "answer_b": " None of these",
        "answer_c": " The hands are moving",
        "answer_d": " Midnight"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the quiz stage of the adventure video game Banjo-Kazooie, failing a question on a Grunty Space will cause the characters to fall into the lava pit.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Gobi is the name of the camel in Gobis Valley in the Banjo and Kazooie video game.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you need to talk to somebody in Kurast Docks in order to activate the first quest in Act III of the computer game Diablo II?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Complete the title of the 2nd quest in Act III of the computer game Diablo II:  Blade of the _____ Religion.",
        "correct_answer": " Old",
        "answer_a": " New",
        "answer_b": " Lost",
        "answer_c": " Old",
        "answer_d": " Found"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the third quest of Act III in Diablo II, how many items must be retrieved?",
        "correct_answer": " 4",
        "answer_a": " 4",
        "answer_b": " 1",
        "answer_c": " 5",
        "answer_d": " 2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who must you talk to, in order to activate the Lam Esens Tome quest in the computer game Diablo II?",
        "correct_answer": " Alkor",
        "answer_a": " Asheara",
        "answer_b": " Ormus",
        "answer_c": " Deckard Cain",
        "answer_d": " Alkor"
    },
    {
        "question": "The 5th quest in Act III of Diablo II is activated by Ormus, only if you are able to find this place.",
        "correct_answer": " Travincal",
        "answer_a": " Kurast Bazaar",
        "answer_b": " Durance of Hate",
        "answer_c": " Upper Kurast",
        "answer_d": " Travincal"
    },
    {
        "question": "What boss must be fought in the last quest in Act III of the computer game Diablo II?",
        "correct_answer": " Mephisto",
        "answer_a": " Andariel",
        "answer_b": " Diablo",
        "answer_c": " Baal",
        "answer_d": " Mephisto"
    },
    {
        "question": "What reward will you receive upon completing the first quest in Act IV of the game Diablo II?",
        "correct_answer": " Two skill points",
        "answer_a": " Free repair",
        "answer_b": " Two skill points",
        "answer_c": " Free potions",
        "answer_d": " Two points in your attributes"
    },
    {
        "question": "You must talk to this person in order to activate your 2nd quest in Act IV of the computer game Diablo II.",
        "correct_answer": " Deckard Cain",
        "answer_a": " Tyrael",
        "answer_b": " Halbu",
        "answer_c": " Jamella",
        "answer_d": " Deckard Cain"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the title of the last quest in Act IV of the computer game Diablo II?",
        "correct_answer": " Terrors End",
        "answer_a": " Diablo: Lord of Terror",
        "answer_b": " Revenge",
        "answer_c": " Terrors End",
        "answer_d": " Restoration of Goodness"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of these songs is NOT in the final section of Guitar Hero III, Lous Inferno?",
        "correct_answer": " Stricken",
        "answer_a": " Stricken",
        "answer_b": " Raining Blood",
        "answer_c": " One",
        "answer_d": " The Number of the Beast"
    },
    {
        "question": "You must beat Guitar Hero III on Expert to be able to play Through the Fire and Flames.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What song is unlocked after beating Tom Morello in a guitar battle in the video game Guitar Hero III?",
        "correct_answer": " Bulls on Parade",
        "answer_a": " Bulls on Parade",
        "answer_b": " She Bangs the Drums",
        "answer_c": " Schools out",
        "answer_d": " Slow Ride"
    },
    {
        "question": "After you beat Guitar Hero III on Expert, you are informed that you can really test your skill by doing this.",
        "correct_answer": " playing Expert in Precision Mode",
        "answer_a": " playing Expert in Precision Mode",
        "answer_b": " playing people online",
        "answer_c": " trying to get 5 stars on every song",
        "answer_d": " battling against a friend"
    },
    {
        "question": "On what date was the release of Call of Duty 4: Modern Warfare announced?",
        "correct_answer": " April 25, 2007",
        "answer_a": " April 25, 2007",
        "answer_b": " March 10, 2007",
        "answer_c": " June 30, 2007",
        "answer_d": " June 22, 2007"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many times can a player trade in their levels at prestige mode in the first-person shooter Call of Duty 4?",
        "correct_answer": " 10",
        "answer_a": " 11",
        "answer_b": " 9",
        "answer_c": " 10",
        "answer_d": " 12"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Xbox 360 version of Call of Duty 4, the achievement war pig is given for killing Khaled Al-Asad.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "The AC-140 gunship has 3 different weapons and uses thermal vision in Call of Duty 4.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Billy Murray lends his voice to Captain Price from Call of Duty 4: Modern Warfare.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who do you have to talk in order to receive your first quest after creating a character in the game Diablo II?",
        "correct_answer": " Akara",
        "answer_a": " Kashya",
        "answer_b": " Akara",
        "answer_c": " Warriv",
        "answer_d": " Charsi"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 2nd quest in the first chapter of the computer game Diablo II?",
        "correct_answer": " Sisters Burial Grounds",
        "answer_a": " The Forgotten Tower",
        "answer_b": " Sisters Burial Grounds",
        "answer_c": " Den of Evil",
        "answer_d": " The Search for Cain"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who must be rescued in the third quest of the game Diablo II?",
        "correct_answer": " Deckard Cain",
        "answer_a": " Deckard Cain",
        "answer_b": " Raven",
        "answer_c": " Gheed",
        "answer_d": " Flavie"
    },
    {
        "question": "What must be retrieved in the fifth quest of the first act of the computer game Diablo II?",
        "correct_answer": " Horadric Malus",
        "answer_a": " Horadric Headpiece",
        "answer_b": " Horadric Staff",
        "answer_c": " Horadric Cube",
        "answer_d": " Horadric Malus"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the last quest in Chapter I of the computer game Diablo II?",
        "correct_answer": " Sisters to the Slaughter",
        "answer_a": " Sisters to the Slaughter",
        "answer_b": " Fathers to the Slaughter",
        "answer_c": " Brothers to the Slaughter",
        "answer_d": " Mothers to the Slaughter"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who must be defeated in the first quest of the second chapter of the computer game Diablo II?",
        "correct_answer": " Radament",
        "answer_a": " Radament",
        "answer_b": " Duriel",
        "answer_c": " Tal Rasha",
        "answer_d": " Summoner"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which item must be formed, to succeed in the second quest of Chapter II of the computer game Diablo II?",
        "correct_answer": " Horadric Staff",
        "answer_a": " Horadric Malus",
        "answer_b": " Horadric Shaft",
        "answer_c": " Horadric Headpiece",
        "answer_d": " Horadric Staff"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your objective of the 4th quest of Chapter II in the game Diablo II?",
        "correct_answer": " to get the Journal",
        "answer_a": " to kill the Summoner",
        "answer_b": " to kill all monsters in the Arcane Sanctuary",
        "answer_c": " to open the portal to the Kurast Docks",
        "answer_d": " to get the Journal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who must be killed in the 5th quest in Chapter II of  Diablo II?",
        "correct_answer": " Summoner",
        "answer_a": " Hell Clan",
        "answer_b": " Summoner",
        "answer_c": " Ghoul Lord",
        "answer_d": " Specter"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who must be saved in the last quest in Chapter II (The Seven Tombs) of the computer game Diablo II?",
        "correct_answer": " Tyrael",
        "answer_a": " Tyrael",
        "answer_b": " Ormus",
        "answer_c": " Jamella",
        "answer_d": " Halbu"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name Master Chiefs partners in the video game Halo 1.",
        "correct_answer": " Green Horns",
        "answer_a": " Alienators",
        "answer_b": " Alien Hunters",
        "answer_c": " Green Toads",
        "answer_d": " Green Horns"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the aliens with the shields in the game Halo 1.",
        "correct_answer": " Jackals",
        "answer_a": " Hunters",
        "answer_b": " Jackals",
        "answer_c": " Grunts",
        "answer_d": " Elites"
    },
    {
        "question": "You start out with a weapon in the first level of Halo 1.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the Halo 1 aliens with plasma cannons?",
        "correct_answer": " Hunters",
        "answer_a": " Hunters",
        "answer_b": " Grunts",
        "answer_c": " Elites",
        "answer_d": " Jackals"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the smallest aliens you face in the video game Halo 1?",
        "correct_answer": " Grunts",
        "answer_a": " Jackals",
        "answer_b": " Hunters",
        "answer_c": " Elites",
        "answer_d": " Grunts"
    },
    {
        "question": "These aliens are the protectors of halo in the video game Halo 1.",
        "correct_answer": " Elites",
        "answer_a": " Jackals",
        "answer_b": " Hunters",
        "answer_c": " Elites",
        "answer_d": " Grunts"
    },
    {
        "question": "Master Chief is the protagonist of the Halo video game.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Samus enemies common to nearly every Metroid video game",
        "correct_answer": " Space Pirates",
        "answer_a": " Space Pirates",
        "answer_b": " The Federation",
        "answer_c": " The Chozo",
        "answer_d": " X Parasites"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the suit Samus starts out with in almost every Metroid video game?",
        "correct_answer": " Varia Suit",
        "answer_a": " Power Suit",
        "answer_b": " Gravity Suit",
        "answer_c": " Varia Suit",
        "answer_d": " Phazon Suit"
    },
    {
        "question": "What word is always attached to the names of the shots that come from Samus arm-mounted gun in the Metroid video game?",
        "correct_answer": " Beam",
        "answer_a": " Beam",
        "answer_b": " Rocket",
        "answer_c": " Gun",
        "answer_d": " Launcher"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of character is Samus from the Metroid video game?",
        "correct_answer": " Human Female",
        "answer_a": " Chozo Male",
        "answer_b": " Human Male",
        "answer_c": " Luminoth Female",
        "answer_d": " Human Female"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Metroid video game, what is Samus profession?",
        "correct_answer": " Bounty Hunter",
        "answer_a": " Professional Collector",
        "answer_b": " Soldier",
        "answer_c": " Pirate",
        "answer_d": " Bounty Hunter"
    },
    {
        "question": "What special abilities are unique to Metroids in the video game series Metroid?",
        "correct_answer": " They can suck out your life energy.",
        "answer_a": " They can suck out your life energy.",
        "answer_b": " They can kill by physical contact.",
        "answer_c": " They can create lifelike illusions.",
        "answer_d": " They can kill by eye contact."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is not an upgrade Samus receives in the Metroid game series?",
        "correct_answer": " Grenade Launcher",
        "answer_a": " Grenade Launcher",
        "answer_b": " Morph Ball",
        "answer_c": " Missile Launcher",
        "answer_d": " Grapple Beam"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Metroid video game series, what species created the suit and most of the upgrades available to Samus?",
        "correct_answer": " The Chozo",
        "answer_a": " The Lords of Science",
        "answer_b": " The Chozo",
        "answer_c": " The Luminoth",
        "answer_d": " The X"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is not an ability available to Samus while in Morph Ball Mode of the Metroid video game?",
        "correct_answer": " Phazon Bomb",
        "answer_a": " Phazon Bomb",
        "answer_b": " Bomb",
        "answer_c": " Power Bomb",
        "answer_d": " Boost Ball"
    },
    {
        "question": "Naruto was first published in 1999, in this magazine.",
        "correct_answer": " Weekly Shonen Jump",
        "answer_a": " Weekly Shonen Run",
        "answer_b": " Weekly Shonen Jump",
        "answer_c": " Monthly Shonen Jump",
        "answer_d": " None of these"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the only female Akatsuki member in the Naruto manga series?",
        "correct_answer": " Konan",
        "answer_a": " Jugo",
        "answer_b": " Madara",
        "answer_c": " Kanan",
        "answer_d": " Konan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the first ninja recruited for the fictional team Hawk?",
        "correct_answer": " Suigetsu Hozuki",
        "answer_a": " Suigetsu Hozuki",
        "answer_b": " Shunsuke Sakuya",
        "answer_c": " Sasuke Uchiha",
        "answer_d": " Akeno Watanabe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Namikaze Sateraito is the opening song for the first 22 episodes of which Naruto season?",
        "correct_answer": " 1",
        "answer_a": " 1",
        "answer_b": " 7",
        "answer_c": " 6",
        "answer_d": " 8"
    },
    {
        "question": "Orochimarus Curse is the title of which volume of the Naruto manga?",
        "correct_answer": " 7",
        "answer_a": " 5",
        "answer_b": " 6",
        "answer_c": " 7",
        "answer_d": " 4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Masatoshi Kazikuga is the author of two novelizations of Naruto, published in Japan and America.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What can you wield after the Monkey Madness Quest in RuneScape?",
        "correct_answer": " Dragon Scimitar",
        "answer_a": " Dragon Scimitar",
        "answer_b": " Dragon Spear",
        "answer_c": " Dragon Halberd",
        "answer_d": " Dragon Longsword"
    },
    {
        "question": "The RuneScape game was created by Christopher Grower.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following RuneScape defence armors is the best?",
        "correct_answer": " Veracs (full)",
        "answer_a": " Dragon (full)",
        "answer_b": " Guthans (full)",
        "answer_c": " Dharoks (full)",
        "answer_d": " Veracs (full)"
    },
    {
        "question": "When was the first version of RuneScape released to the public?",
        "correct_answer": " January 4th 2001",
        "answer_a": " July 4th, 2003",
        "answer_b": " Febuary 8th 1998",
        "answer_c": " January 4th 2001",
        "answer_d": " June 5th 2001"
    },
    {
        "question": "RuneScape is set in the fantasy-themed realm of Gielinor.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "The creator of RuneScape was helped by his cousin, Joel, in developing the game.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was RuneScape originally named?",
        "correct_answer": " DeviousMUD",
        "answer_a": " DeviousMUD",
        "answer_b": " Runeworld",
        "answer_c": " DeviousWOF",
        "answer_d": " RuneLand"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the evil god in RunesSape whose rival is Saradomin?",
        "correct_answer": " Zamorak",
        "answer_a": " Guthan",
        "answer_b": " Guthix",
        "answer_c": " Dharok",
        "answer_d": " Zamorak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Are there members-only servers for RuneScape Classic?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "What weapon do you wield after the Regicide Quest in RuneScape?",
        "correct_answer": " Dragon hally",
        "answer_a": " Dragon hally",
        "answer_b": " Flaming sword of death",
        "answer_c": " Dragon longsword",
        "answer_d": " Dagon scimitar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ash Ketchum, the main protagonist in the Pok\u00c3\u00a9mon anime, is loosely based on what other character?",
        "correct_answer": " Red",
        "answer_a": " Blue",
        "answer_b": " Green",
        "answer_c": " Red",
        "answer_d": " Yellow"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what way can you evolve the Pokemon Gilgar into Gliscor in the Diamond and Pearl Pokemon series for Nintendo DS?",
        "correct_answer": " none of these",
        "answer_a": " none of these",
        "answer_b": " train it at night",
        "answer_c": " Trade it while holding a razor fang",
        "answer_d": " trade it"
    },
    {
        "question": "Celebi is a grass type Pokemon that you can find in the sinnow region.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a game in The Last Half of Darkness series?",
        "correct_answer": " The Last Half of Darkness: New Ways to Die",
        "answer_a": " The Last Half of Darkness 3",
        "answer_b": " The Last Half of Darkness: Shadows of the Servants",
        "answer_c": " The Last Half of Darkness VGA",
        "answer_d": " The Last Half of Darkness: New Ways to Die"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is not the title of an actual PC game?",
        "correct_answer": " Last Warrior of Orion",
        "answer_a": " Power Rangers Time Force",
        "answer_b": " Last Warrior of Orion",
        "answer_c": " Master of Magic",
        "answer_d": " Archon Ultra"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is part of the game Archon Ultra?",
        "correct_answer": " Valkyrie",
        "answer_a": " Valkyrie",
        "answer_b": " Black Knight",
        "answer_c": " Witch",
        "answer_d": " Orc"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Last Half of Darkness series, there is a Last Half of Darkness III VGA.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these horror movie based games isnt a PC game?",
        "correct_answer": " Blade",
        "answer_a": " The Mist",
        "answer_b": " Alien Trilogy",
        "answer_c": " Blade",
        "answer_d": " Clive Barkers Undying"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these games was not developed by New World Computing?",
        "correct_answer": " X-COM: UFO Defense",
        "answer_a": " Heroes of Might and Magic",
        "answer_b": " Planets Edge",
        "answer_c": " Might and Magic",
        "answer_d": " X-COM: UFO Defense"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not an adventure game?",
        "correct_answer": " Raptor: Call of the Shadows",
        "answer_a": " Dragon Lore: The Legend Begins",
        "answer_b": " Raptor: Call of the Shadows",
        "answer_c": " The Nine Lives of the Secret Agent Katt",
        "answer_d": " 7th Guest"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of game is Power Rangers Time Force?",
        "correct_answer": " All of these",
        "answer_a": " All of these",
        "answer_b": " 3D Action game",
        "answer_c": " Mini-game collection",
        "answer_d": " 2D Side-scroller"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who created the game Last Half of Darkness?",
        "correct_answer": " William R. Fisher III",
        "answer_a": " Brian Moriarty",
        "answer_b": " Bill Gates",
        "answer_c": " William R. Fisher III",
        "answer_d": " Roberta Williams"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a real role-playing game?",
        "correct_answer": " Last Guardian",
        "answer_a": " Albion",
        "answer_b": " Dungeon Master",
        "answer_c": " Last Guardian",
        "answer_d": " Bloodnet"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the evil dragon in RuneScape that players have to kill in the Dragon Slayer quest?",
        "correct_answer": " Elvarg",
        "answer_a": " Elvarg",
        "answer_b": " Delrith",
        "answer_c": " Hector",
        "answer_d": " Verac"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the RuneScape game, on the Construction Skillcape emote, the character performing the emote does which of the following?",
        "correct_answer": " Builds a small house around himself",
        "answer_a": " Builds a small house around himself",
        "answer_b": " Hammers down nails on a board",
        "answer_c": " Makes a workbench with a saw",
        "answer_d": " Builds a bridge"
    },
    {
        "question": "To equip Barrows armour and weapons in RuneScape, you must have an attack and defence level 70.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is it true that in the RuneScape game, goblins can be found only in Goblin Village and Goblin Cave?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the RuneScape game, you need to have 80 defence to use Guthix armor.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the reward in RuneScapes 2008 Easter Seasonal Event?",
        "correct_answer": " a chocatrice cape that turns you into a wrapped egg",
        "answer_a": " a chocolate sword that you can eat off of 3 times a day healing 10hp",
        "answer_b": " a chocatrice cape that turns you into a wrapped egg",
        "answer_c": " Easter bunny ears that make your speed increase",
        "answer_d": " a giant cookie"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the mime random event in RuneScape, the object is to identify all the mime emotes and get a reward afterwards.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "To start the Demon Slayer Quest in RuneScape, you must talk to which one of these?",
        "correct_answer": " The Gypsy",
        "answer_a": " a dwarf",
        "answer_b": " The Gypsy",
        "answer_c": " Sir Vyrinn",
        "answer_d": " The duke of Lumbridge"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what RuneScape quest do you have to use a friend from the opposite gang?",
        "correct_answer": " Shield of Arrav",
        "answer_a": " Dragon Slayer",
        "answer_b": " Shield of Arrav",
        "answer_c": " Vampire Slayer",
        "answer_d": " Romeo and Juliet"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the game Super Mario Kart, how many coins do you receive for placing 1st in a single race?",
        "correct_answer": " 9",
        "answer_a": " 15",
        "answer_b": " 9",
        "answer_c": " 10",
        "answer_d": " 12"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do players have lives in the racing game Super Mario Kart?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the game Super Mario Kart, what does the mushroom item do to the racer?",
        "correct_answer": " gives the racer a short burst of speed",
        "answer_a": " poisons the racer so they cant steer correctly",
        "answer_b": " gives the racer a short burst of speed",
        "answer_c": " makes the racer large to run over other racers",
        "answer_d": " slows the racer so they dont go as fast"
    },
    {
        "question": "All of the following cups are in the game Super Mario Kart, except which one of these?",
        "correct_answer": " Lightning cup",
        "answer_a": " Star cup",
        "answer_b": " Mushroom cup",
        "answer_c": " Special cup",
        "answer_d": " Lightning cup"
    },
    {
        "question": "The feather item in the game Super Mario Kart helps the racer by jumping.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Flower cup, in the game Super Mario Kart, on which track do you start?",
        "correct_answer": " Choco Island",
        "answer_a": " Donut Plains 2",
        "answer_b": " Choco Island",
        "answer_c": " Koopa Beach 1",
        "answer_d": " Mario Circuit 1"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Super Mario Kart, the green shell is a heat-seeking missile.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the game Super Mario Kart, for the Super Nintendo, it is possible to fall off the track.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "All of the following are items used in the game Super Mario Kart, for the Super NES, except which one of the following?",
        "correct_answer": " blue shell",
        "answer_a": " coins",
        "answer_b": " banana peel",
        "answer_c": " ghost",
        "answer_d": " blue shell"
    },
    {
        "question": "On the Nintendo 64 version of Mario Kart, Wario replaced which of the following playable characters from the Super NES version?",
        "correct_answer": " Koopa Troopa",
        "answer_a": " Princess Peach",
        "answer_b": " Koopa Troopa",
        "answer_c": " Donkey Kong",
        "answer_d": " Yoshi"
    },
    {
        "question": "There is a PC port in the first three Timesplitters games.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many of the following Power Rangers games are for PC: Power Rangers; Power Rangers: Lightspeed Rescue; Power Rangers: Super Legends; Power Rangers Zeo Versus the Machine Empire; Power Rangers: Ninja Storm Double Pack?",
        "correct_answer": " 5",
        "answer_a": " 5",
        "answer_b": " 4",
        "answer_c": " 2",
        "answer_d": " 1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Excluding collections, how many Might and Magic games were released from 1986 to 2002?",
        "correct_answer": " 11",
        "answer_a": " 11",
        "answer_b": " 9",
        "answer_c": " 10",
        "answer_d": " 7"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Might and Magic 8, which of these classes are unselectable for the main character?",
        "correct_answer": " Dragon",
        "answer_a": " Vampire",
        "answer_b": " Dark Elf",
        "answer_c": " Knight",
        "answer_d": " Dragon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Joe Satriani was given a special thanks in B.A.T. II.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which of these games does the player take the role of Kirt?",
        "correct_answer": " Shadowcaster",
        "answer_a": " Marvel: Ultimate Alliance",
        "answer_b": " Quest for Glory",
        "answer_c": " Freedom Force",
        "answer_d": " Shadowcaster"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these games is rogue-like?",
        "correct_answer": " Ancient Domains of Mystery",
        "answer_a": " Neverwinter Nights",
        "answer_b": " Baldurs Gate",
        "answer_c": " The Elder Scrolls 4 Obvilion",
        "answer_d": " Ancient Domains of Mystery"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many races are there in Star Wars: Galactic Battlegrounds? (With expansion)",
        "correct_answer": " 8",
        "answer_a": " 12",
        "answer_b": " 7",
        "answer_c": " 8",
        "answer_d": " 6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do you transform into in stage 4 of Altered Beast?",
        "correct_answer": " Weretiger",
        "answer_a": " Werewolf",
        "answer_b": " Werebear",
        "answer_c": " Weredragon",
        "answer_d": " Weretiger"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these games isnt an action/adventure hybrid?",
        "correct_answer": " Grand Theft Auto",
        "answer_a": " Grand Theft Auto",
        "answer_b": " Kings Quest: Mask of Eternity",
        "answer_c": " The Nine Lives of the Secret Agent Katt",
        "answer_d": " The Adventures of Maddog Williams"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the protagonist of the PC game Blood?",
        "correct_answer": " Caleb",
        "answer_a": " Ellen Ripley",
        "answer_b": " Hugo",
        "answer_c": " Blake Stone",
        "answer_d": " Caleb"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these isnt a game from the Hugo series?",
        "correct_answer": " Hugos Castle of Death",
        "answer_a": " Hugos Castle of Death",
        "answer_b": " Hugos House of Horror",
        "answer_c": " Nightmare 3D",
        "answer_d": " Whodunit?"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the odd game.",
        "correct_answer": " Archon",
        "answer_a": " The Terminator",
        "answer_b": " Doom",
        "answer_c": " Twilight 2000",
        "answer_d": " Archon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these games was not developed by Blizzard?",
        "correct_answer": " Hammer of the Gods",
        "answer_a": " Blackthrone",
        "answer_b": " Diablo",
        "answer_c": " The Lost Vikings",
        "answer_d": " Hammer of the Gods"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these games was developed by New World Computing?",
        "correct_answer": " Planets Edge",
        "answer_a": " Pizza Tycoon",
        "answer_b": " Planets Edge",
        "answer_c": " Blackthrone",
        "answer_d": " One Must Fall 2097"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these isnt a Sega collection for PC?",
        "correct_answer": " Sega Genesis Collection",
        "answer_a": " Sega Genesis Collection",
        "answer_b": " Sonic 3 and Knuckles",
        "answer_c": " Sega Smash Pack",
        "answer_d": " Sonic Adventure DX: Directors Cut"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Nancy Drew conputer games, Nancy Drews trusty sidekicks are cousins George Fayne and this slightly plump blonde.",
        "correct_answer": " Bess",
        "answer_a": " Jenny",
        "answer_b": " Beth",
        "answer_c": " Bess",
        "answer_d": " Tess"
    },
    {
        "question": "These two detective brothers appear several times in the Nancy Drew computer games to help Nancy solve mysteries.",
        "correct_answer": " Frank and Joe",
        "answer_a": " Frank and Joe",
        "answer_b": " Frank and Moe",
        "answer_c": " Fred and Joseph",
        "answer_d": " None of these"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the very first Nancy Drew computer game?",
        "correct_answer": " Secrets Can Kill",
        "answer_a": " Treasure in the Royal Tower",
        "answer_b": " Secrets Can Kill",
        "answer_c": " Message in a Haunted Mansion",
        "answer_d": " Secret of the Old Clock"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did Nancy Drew find along with a message in the computer game Message in a Haunted Mansion?",
        "correct_answer": " A shark tooth",
        "answer_a": " A piece of glass",
        "answer_b": " A bat wing",
        "answer_c": " She did not find anything along with the note.",
        "answer_d": " A shark tooth"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which of these computer games did Nancy Drew wake up in the middle of the night because of a nightmare?",
        "correct_answer": " Ghost of Blackmoor Manor",
        "answer_a": " Creature of Kapu Cave",
        "answer_b": " Secrets Can Kill",
        "answer_c": " She never had a nightmare.",
        "answer_d": " Ghost of Blackmoor Manor"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these characters appears in the Nancy Drew computer game Lights, Camera, Curses!?",
        "correct_answer": " Molly McOwens",
        "answer_a": " Rick Arlen",
        "answer_b": " None of these",
        "answer_c": " Molly McOwens",
        "answer_d": " Sally McDonald"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the computer game Warnings at Waverly Academy, what was pictured on Nancy Drews cabin door?",
        "correct_answer": " Mr. Mingles, the cat",
        "answer_a": " Mr. Mingles, the cat",
        "answer_b": " A butterfly with you and your roommates names in it",
        "answer_c": " it was blank",
        "answer_d": " The Waverly Academy crow"
    },
    {
        "question": "Rick Arlen is known as an arrogant television star from Stay Tuned for Danger, but his picture appears in what place in another Nancy Drew game?",
        "correct_answer": " In a briefcase",
        "answer_a": " His picture never appears in another game",
        "answer_b": " In a briefcase",
        "answer_c": " In a bottle",
        "answer_d": " In a bedside picture frame"
    },
    {
        "question": "The wolf in the computer game White Wolf of Icicle Creek was named Isis.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the computer game The Final Scene, a flashing ring gave Nancy Drew the opportunity to save a friend.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Nancy Drew computer game Ghost Dogs of Moon Lake, what is the rangers last name?",
        "correct_answer": " Smith",
        "answer_a": " Smith",
        "answer_b": " Wilkinson",
        "answer_c": " Madison",
        "answer_d": " His last name was never revealed"
    },
    {
        "question": "When you first start Wonderland Online, where do you find yourself?",
        "correct_answer": " On a ship",
        "answer_a": " On a ship",
        "answer_b": " On an island",
        "answer_c": " On a dock",
        "answer_d": " In a volcano"
    },
    {
        "question": "When your raft gets washed up, what is the place it lands (for the first time) in the game Wonderland Online?",
        "correct_answer": " Starter Beach",
        "answer_a": " Beginners Island",
        "answer_b": " Tutorial Ridge",
        "answer_c": " Starter Beach",
        "answer_d": " Newbie Point"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of these is not a jelly monster you can find on North Island in the game Wonderland Online?",
        "correct_answer": " Pear",
        "answer_a": " Pineapple",
        "answer_b": " Pear",
        "answer_c": " Kiwi",
        "answer_d": " Grape"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Wonderland Online, which of these makes your level go up?",
        "correct_answer": " Killing monsters",
        "answer_a": " Killing monsters",
        "answer_b": " Fishing",
        "answer_c": " Setting up shops",
        "answer_d": " Compounding items"
    },
    {
        "question": "You can ride beasts that you capture in the game Wonderland Online.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Wonderland Online it is possible to have a dinosaur as a pet.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What game starts when you talk to some fierce rabbits at Kelan Village in Wonderland Online?",
        "correct_answer": " Reaction",
        "answer_a": " Operation",
        "answer_b": " Situation",
        "answer_c": " Conversation",
        "answer_d": " Reaction"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does a mermaid at North Island ask you to fetch for her as a quest in the game Wonderland Online?",
        "correct_answer": " A shell",
        "answer_a": " Her true love",
        "answer_b": " Her will",
        "answer_c": " A message in a bottle",
        "answer_d": " A shell"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many characters in Super Smash Bros Brawl have the Final Smash Attack of Landmaster?",
        "correct_answer": " 3",
        "answer_a": " none",
        "answer_b": " 3",
        "answer_c": " 2",
        "answer_d": " 4"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many characters are there at the beginning of Super Smash Bros Brawl?",
        "correct_answer": " 20",
        "answer_a": " 19",
        "answer_b": " 15",
        "answer_c": " 21",
        "answer_d": " 20"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many Super Smash Bros Brawl characters have 2+ characters in their team?",
        "correct_answer": " 5",
        "answer_a": " 6",
        "answer_b": " 5",
        "answer_c": " 4",
        "answer_d": " 3"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many bosses are there in Subspace Emissary in Super Smash Bros Brawl?",
        "correct_answer": " 8",
        "answer_a": " 10",
        "answer_b": " 9",
        "answer_c": " 8",
        "answer_d": " 5"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the bosses in the first Metroid game?",
        "correct_answer": " Ridley, Kraid, Mother Brain",
        "answer_a": " Alpha Metroid, Gamma Metroid, Zeta Metroid, Omega Metroid, Queen Metroid",
        "answer_b": " Ridley, Mother Brain, Queen Metroid",
        "answer_c": " Ridley, Kraid, Mother Brain",
        "answer_d": " Ridley, Kraid, Queen Metroid"
    },
    {
        "question": "Chronologically what is the last boss Samus has faced in the Metroid series?",
        "correct_answer": " Omega Metroid",
        "answer_a": " Omega Metroid",
        "answer_b": " Queen Metroid",
        "answer_c": " Mother Brain",
        "answer_d": " Aurora Unit 313"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Metroid Prime 3: Corruption Samus fights Meta Ridley while falling down which of the following?",
        "correct_answer": " Generator Shaft",
        "answer_a": " Elevator Shaft",
        "answer_b": " Generator Shaft",
        "answer_c": " Ventilation System",
        "answer_d": " Garbage Disposal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why is Phatoons eye his weak point in the Metroid series?",
        "correct_answer": " His eye is the only thing that connects him to the material world.",
        "answer_a": " He will run away if blinded.",
        "answer_b": " His eye is the only thing that connects him to the material world.",
        "answer_c": " His eye is his only weapon.",
        "answer_d": " It is unknown."
    },
    {
        "question": "The Pinnacle of Project Helix is what kind of Phazon Infused Space Pirate?",
        "correct_answer": " Omega Pirate",
        "answer_a": " Berserker Lord",
        "answer_b": " Berserker Knight",
        "answer_c": " Omega Pirate",
        "answer_d": " Elite Pirate"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Metroid series, the Vorashs weak point is its eyes.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "The final boss of Metroid Other M on hard mode is Phantoon.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Nightmares main weapon in the Metroid series?",
        "correct_answer": " Multi-laser system",
        "answer_a": " Gravity Manipultain Device",
        "answer_b": " Phazon Cannons",
        "answer_c": " The ability to create hallucinations",
        "answer_d": " Multi-laser system"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Berserker Lord is fought twice in the Metorid series.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where does the first game of the Crysis series take place?",
        "correct_answer": " Lingshan Islands",
        "answer_a": " Mars",
        "answer_b": " Caribbean Islands",
        "answer_c": " Lingshan Islands",
        "answer_d": " North Korea"
    },
    {
        "question": "Of the Crysis characters below, who is not a member of Raptor Team?",
        "correct_answer": " Alcatraz",
        "answer_a": " Psycho",
        "answer_b": " Alcatraz",
        "answer_c": " Aztec",
        "answer_d": " Prophet"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Crysis character founded C.E.L.L?",
        "correct_answer": " Jacob Hargreave",
        "answer_a": " Jacob Hargreave",
        "answer_b": " Dr. Gould",
        "answer_c": " Tara Strickland",
        "answer_d": " Major Lockhart"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which city is not a Ceph point of interest in the Crysis game series?",
        "correct_answer": " Paris",
        "answer_a": " London",
        "answer_b": " Paris",
        "answer_c": " Cairo",
        "answer_d": " Hawaii"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Crysis games Ceph Organisms are nicknamed Stalkers.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the Typhoons Rate of Fire in the Crysis games?",
        "correct_answer": " 500 Rounds Per second",
        "answer_a": " 500 Rounds per minute",
        "answer_b": " 720 Rounds per second",
        "answer_c": " None, the Typhoon fires a beam that you must focus on the target",
        "answer_d": " 500 Rounds Per second"
    },
    {
        "question": "You can not destroy a round from the Gravity Bomb Launcher in the Crysis games.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Prophet dies at the beginning of Crysis 2 .",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Crysis games, Pingers do not fire at Alcatraz when he is cloaked.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year was Crysis character Jacob Hargreave born?",
        "correct_answer": " 1896",
        "answer_a": " 1967",
        "answer_b": " 1896",
        "answer_c": " 2001",
        "answer_d": " 1919"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which map is considered as a remake of the much loved Halo 3 map Valhalla?",
        "correct_answer": " Ragnarok",
        "answer_a": " Exile",
        "answer_b": " Haven",
        "answer_c": " Vortex",
        "answer_d": " Ragnarok"
    },
    {
        "question": "The plasma rifle is the first covenant weapon to be unlocked in the multiplayer mode of Halo 4.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the only two weapons you can use in Grifball in Halo 4 Multiplayer?",
        "correct_answer": " Gravity Hammer and Energy Sword",
        "answer_a": " Gravity Hammer and Energy Sword",
        "answer_b": " Sniper Rifle and Binary Rifle",
        "answer_c": " Rocket Launcher and Incinerator Canon",
        "answer_d": " Storm Rifle and Supressor"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the award you get for infecting every player in Flood mode in Halo 4 Multiplayer?",
        "correct_answer": " Gravemind",
        "answer_a": " Hunter",
        "answer_b": " Gravemind",
        "answer_c": " Floodifier",
        "answer_d": " Flood Master"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which  Halo 4 Multiplayer map has a Mantis being constructed in the center of the map?",
        "correct_answer": " None",
        "answer_a": " Adrift",
        "answer_b": " None",
        "answer_c": " Ragnarok",
        "answer_d": " Longbow"
    },
    {
        "question": "You can drop weapons of your choice in Halo 4.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "On what ship does the Halo 4 Multiplayer take place?",
        "correct_answer": " UNSC Infinity",
        "answer_a": " UNSC Pillar of Autumn",
        "answer_b": " UNSC Infinity",
        "answer_c": " UNSC Spirit of Fire",
        "answer_d": " None"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Binary Rifle in Halo 4 can only kill someone with a headshot.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the Promethean pistol called in Halo 4?",
        "correct_answer": " Boltshot",
        "answer_a": " Hardlight Pistol",
        "answer_b": " Plasma Pistol",
        "answer_c": " Light Pistol",
        "answer_d": " Boltshot"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which armor ability allows the user to see through walls in Halo 4?",
        "correct_answer": " Promethean Vision",
        "answer_a": " Advanced Vision googles",
        "answer_b": " Promethean Vision",
        "answer_c": " X-ray Vision",
        "answer_d": " Heat Scanner"
    },
    {
        "question": "What happens when you die in the 2006 Runescape Halloween Event?",
        "correct_answer": " The Grim Reaper comes to claim your body.",
        "answer_a": " You burst into flames of different colors.",
        "answer_b": " The Grim Reaper comes to claim your body.",
        "answer_c": " Saradomin reincarnates your body after you die.",
        "answer_d": " nothing"
    },
    {
        "question": "Jagex Ltd released RuneScape 3 in 2004.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Runescape a chicken is a level 1 monster.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Zezima is the name of a Runescape player who was first ranked number 1 in 2003.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "When were Runescape Bots introduced?",
        "correct_answer": " January 2001",
        "answer_a": " September 2001",
        "answer_b": " January 2001",
        "answer_c": " May 1997",
        "answer_d": " January 1997"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many sub-quests are there in the quest Recipe for Disaster?",
        "correct_answer": " 10",
        "answer_a": " six",
        "answer_b": " 91",
        "answer_c": " 5",
        "answer_d": " 10"
    },
    {
        "question": "The King Black Dragon was the highest level monster in Runescape until 7 September 2004, when it was replaced by which of the following?",
        "correct_answer": " The Kalphite Queen",
        "answer_a": " Mithril Dragon",
        "answer_b": " Dust Devil",
        "answer_c": " None of these",
        "answer_d": " The Kalphite Queen"
    },
    {
        "question": "Did any Runescape player manage to kill the Corporal Beast by themselves without abusing a glitch during the first year of the Beasts release?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "On Tutorial Island of RuneScape you get runes from a male character.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these RuneScape weapons is the most powerful?",
        "correct_answer": " Ahrims staff",
        "answer_a": " Ancient staff",
        "answer_b": " Sardomin staff",
        "answer_c": " Iban staff",
        "answer_d": " Ahrims staff"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is the best type of RuneScape weapon for non members?",
        "correct_answer": " Dragon",
        "answer_a": " Rune",
        "answer_b": " Granite",
        "answer_c": " Barrow",
        "answer_d": " Dragon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these RuneScape quests is the most difficult?",
        "correct_answer": " Monkey Madness",
        "answer_a": " Final Showdown of Death",
        "answer_b": " Prince Ali Rescue",
        "answer_c": " Monkey Madness",
        "answer_d": " Dragon Slayer"
    },
    {
        "question": "Christopher Greenfield is the creator of the RuneScape game.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "The creator of RuneScape was helped by his cousin in developing the game.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is is true that in RuneScape, the Corporeal Beast is level 311, the highest level?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a place in RuneScape?",
        "correct_answer": " Duel Wars",
        "answer_a": " Bounty Hunter",
        "answer_b": " Duel Wars",
        "answer_c": " Castle Wars",
        "answer_d": " Clan Wars"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the female character and one of the four survivors in LFD1.",
        "correct_answer": " Zoey",
        "answer_a": " Marylin",
        "answer_b": " Zoey",
        "answer_c": " Roxanne",
        "answer_d": " Mimi"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main difference between LFD1 and LFD2 in regard to use of weapons?",
        "correct_answer": " In LFD1 there are no melee weapons like the ax or the machete.",
        "answer_a": " In LFD2 you can use a flame thrower.",
        "answer_b": " In LFD1 there are no melee weapons like the ax or the machete.",
        "answer_c": " In LFD1 there are no pipe bombs.",
        "answer_d": " In LFD2 you can throw hand grenades."
    },
    {
        "question": "Setting off a car alarm scares off the zombies in LFD.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "A pipe bomb is an ideal weapon to destroy LFD zombies because it is a silent weapon and they wont hear it when you throw it among a group of them.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Unlike in other video or PC games you cannot save a game in LFD and then come back later to play it from where you left off.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the fictional government agency or organization that was supposed to fight the infection and evacuate people from infected areas in LFD.",
        "correct_answer": " CEDA",
        "answer_a": " CEDA",
        "answer_b": " UNSC",
        "answer_c": " PETA",
        "answer_d": " USAA"
    },
    {
        "question": "In LFD2 the Parish campaign takes place in this city.",
        "correct_answer": " New Orleans",
        "answer_a": " Savannah",
        "answer_b": " Miami",
        "answer_c": " Atlanta",
        "answer_d": " New Orleans"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of fictional band featured in LFD2?",
        "correct_answer": " The Midnight Riders",
        "answer_a": " The Runarounds",
        "answer_b": " The Rockabillies",
        "answer_c": " Stagnant Water",
        "answer_d": " The Midnight Riders"
    },
    {
        "question": "What pestilence or disease caused people to turn into zombies and deformed some of them into super mutants in LFD?",
        "correct_answer": " The green flu",
        "answer_a": " Swines disease",
        "answer_b": " The mutant virus",
        "answer_c": " Nuclear malaria",
        "answer_d": " The green flu"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the race car driver encountered in the Dead Center campaign of LFD2?",
        "correct_answer": " Jimmy Gibbs Jr.",
        "answer_a": " Hank Buffet",
        "answer_b": " Speedy Weedy",
        "answer_c": " Jimmy Gibbs Jr.",
        "answer_d": " Herb Gonzales"
    },
    {
        "question": "In LFD1 the achievement known as Do Not Disturb is awarded for which of the following?",
        "correct_answer": " Sneaking past all Witches in a campaign without disturbing one",
        "answer_a": " Not interrupting a fellow survivor when he is busy shooting at one of the zombies",
        "answer_b": " Not waking up your fellow survivors while they are sleeping in the safehouse",
        "answer_c": " Not disturbing a zombie while its eating someone",
        "answer_d": " Sneaking past all Witches in a campaign without disturbing one"
    },
    {
        "question": "In LFD2 the achievement known as the CHAIN OF COMMAND is awarded for which of the following?",
        "correct_answer": " Killing 100 Common Infected with the chainsaw",
        "answer_a": " Tying up one of the special infected with some chain",
        "answer_b": " Using a chainsaw to cut through some dense brush",
        "answer_c": " Killing 100 Common Infected with the chainsaw",
        "answer_d": " Whipping one of the zombies with a piece of chain"
    },
    {
        "question": "You can add more maps and campaigns in LFD1 and LFD2.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In both LFD1 and LFD2, accumulating more cash than the other survivors will give you an advantage.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What unique Zord do the Time Force Rangers have?",
        "correct_answer": " Time Shadow",
        "answer_a": " Time Shadow",
        "answer_b": " Last Time",
        "answer_c": " Time Knight",
        "answer_d": " Dark Time"
    },
    {
        "question": "Zelda, featured in The Legend of Zelda series of video games, is what kind of character?",
        "correct_answer": " The princess",
        "answer_a": " The main villain",
        "answer_b": " The old lady",
        "answer_c": " The princess",
        "answer_d": " The elfin hero"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the currency used in the Legend of Zelda video game series?",
        "correct_answer": " Rupees",
        "answer_a": " Coins",
        "answer_b": " Triangles",
        "answer_c": " Rings",
        "answer_d": " Rupees"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is not a race featured in the Legend of Zelda video games?",
        "correct_answer": " Hobbit",
        "answer_a": " Zora",
        "answer_b": " Hylian",
        "answer_c": " Hobbit",
        "answer_d": " Rito"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these items is always in Links arsenal in the Legend of Zelda games?",
        "correct_answer": " Boomerang",
        "answer_a": " Boomerang",
        "answer_b": " Wand of Gamelon",
        "answer_c": " Hookshot",
        "answer_d": " Magic cape"
    },
    {
        "question": "In The Legend of Zelda series of video games Zelda possesses which piece of the Triforce?",
        "correct_answer": " Wisdom",
        "answer_a": " Power",
        "answer_b": " Wisdom",
        "answer_c": " All of them",
        "answer_d": " Courage"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is there a game called Super Mario Tennis?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "There are Mario games featuring racing, baseball, soccer, tennis, and golf.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following characters is NOT a sidekick in Super Mario Strikers?",
        "correct_answer": " Paratroopa",
        "answer_a": " Paratroopa",
        "answer_b": " Birdo",
        "answer_c": " Toad",
        "answer_d": " Hammer bros."
    },
    {
        "question": "In Mario Superstar Baseball what do you have to you use to unleash your characters super pitch?",
        "correct_answer": " A star",
        "answer_a": " A heart",
        "answer_b": " A fire flower",
        "answer_c": " A star",
        "answer_d": " A credit"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Mario Kart, characters are classified as either heavy or light.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Luigis power shot in Mario Power Tennis?",
        "correct_answer": " A hammer",
        "answer_a": " He sucks the ball with a vacuum.",
        "answer_b": " He jumps really high and slams the ball.",
        "answer_c": " A hammer",
        "answer_d": " A super big tennis racket"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Mario Power Tennis, Bowsers racket has spikes on it.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the most basic court in Mario Power Tennis?",
        "correct_answer": " Peach Dome",
        "answer_a": " Mario Mansion",
        "answer_b": " Peach Palace",
        "answer_c": " Peach Dome",
        "answer_d": " Mario Yard"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sonic the Hedgehog is the protagonist of a video game, released by Nintendo.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of these game systems was released by Nintendo?",
        "correct_answer": " snes",
        "answer_a": " Playstation",
        "answer_b": " None of these",
        "answer_c": " snes",
        "answer_d": " Xbox"
    },
    {
        "question": "Does Nintendos mascot Mario wear a red and black hat?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is it true that Kirby, the protagonist of the Kirby game series, is pink?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Captain Falcon, from the F-Zero video games, is a pirate.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these games was not released by Nintendo?",
        "correct_answer": " Assassins Creed",
        "answer_a": " Warioware",
        "answer_b": " Mario Galaxy",
        "answer_c": " Assassins Creed",
        "answer_d": " Star Fox"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Super Smash Bros. Melee character can be unlocked by defeating the 10-minute melee?",
        "correct_answer": " Falco",
        "answer_a": " Falco",
        "answer_b": " Jigglypuff",
        "answer_c": " Roy",
        "answer_d": " Mr. Game and Watch"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character in Super Smash Bros. Melee can be unlocked by beating the game with every character?",
        "correct_answer": " Mr. Game and Watch",
        "answer_a": " Luigi",
        "answer_b": " Falco",
        "answer_c": " Mr. Game and Watch",
        "answer_d": " Roy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character in Super Smash Bros. Melee did not have a grapple ability?",
        "correct_answer": " Zelda",
        "answer_a": " Zelda",
        "answer_b": " Young Link",
        "answer_c": " Link",
        "answer_d": " Samus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Pokemon character in Super Smash Bros. Melee damages itself by using its B button moves?",
        "correct_answer": " Pichu",
        "answer_a": " Mewtwo",
        "answer_b": " Jigglypuff",
        "answer_c": " Pichu",
        "answer_d": " Pikachu"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character in Super Smash Bros. Melee is the final boss of the normal game (Classic Mode)?",
        "correct_answer": " Master Hand",
        "answer_a": " Poorly Coordinated Hand",
        "answer_b": " Crazy Hand",
        "answer_c": " Master Hand",
        "answer_d": " Power Hand"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character in Super Smash Bros. Melee could jump more than once in midair?",
        "correct_answer": " Kirby",
        "answer_a": " Peach",
        "answer_b": " Meta Knight",
        "answer_c": " Kirby",
        "answer_d": " Yoshi"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character in Super Smash Bros. Melee is unlocked by beating the game with a character from the same game?",
        "correct_answer": " Roy",
        "answer_a": " Falco",
        "answer_b": " Mewtwo",
        "answer_c": " Roy",
        "answer_d": " Captain Falcon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character in Super Smash Bros. Melee had the ability to pick up other characters and walk with them?",
        "correct_answer": " Donkey Kong",
        "answer_a": " Ganondorf",
        "answer_b": " Donkey Kong",
        "answer_c": " Bowser",
        "answer_d": " Mario"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following game series featured the most Super Smash Bros. Melee characters?",
        "correct_answer": " Mario",
        "answer_a": " Zelda",
        "answer_b": " Mario",
        "answer_c": " Star Fox",
        "answer_d": " Pokemon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character in Super Smash Bros. Melee does not have a saving Up B button move?",
        "correct_answer": " Yoshi",
        "answer_a": " Yoshi",
        "answer_b": " Bowser",
        "answer_c": " Dr. Mario",
        "answer_d": " Peach"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the main character in the 2006 third-person shooter Gears of War?",
        "correct_answer": " Marcus Fenix",
        "answer_a": " Marcus Fenix",
        "answer_b": " Lt. Kim",
        "answer_c": " Dominic Santiago",
        "answer_d": " Baird"
    },
    {
        "question": "In video game Gears of War, these creatures let loose loud piercing shrieks when they attack but are generally easy to kill.",
        "correct_answer": " Wretches",
        "answer_a": " Wretches",
        "answer_b": " Drones",
        "answer_c": " Corpsers",
        "answer_d": " Theron Guards"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Gears of War, if you stay in the dark and walk slowly, the mutant race Kryll wont attack you.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Gears of War, which of these creatures is blind, walks upright and hunts by smell?",
        "correct_answer": " Berserker",
        "answer_a": " Drone",
        "answer_b": " Corpser",
        "answer_c": " Berserker",
        "answer_d": " Wretch"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the third-person shooter Gears of War, can you kill the Corpser in the Locust tunnels by using the Hammer of Dawn?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the Colonel who is in command according to the scenarios in Gears of War?",
        "correct_answer": " Hoffman",
        "answer_a": " Raam",
        "answer_b": " Cole",
        "answer_c": " Hoffman",
        "answer_d": " Santiago"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Gears of War game, which member of Alpha Team is first found fighting in a small courtyard, alone and taunting the Locust?",
        "correct_answer": " Cole",
        "answer_a": " Cole",
        "answer_b": " Baird",
        "answer_c": " Rojas",
        "answer_d": " Kim"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which difficulty setting can only be unlocked by completing Gears of War once on any difficulty?",
        "correct_answer": " Insane",
        "answer_a": " Normal",
        "answer_b": " Casual",
        "answer_c": " Insane",
        "answer_d": " Hardcore"
    },
    {
        "question": "General RAAM is protected by the mutant race Kryll when you try to kill him on the train at the end of Gears of War.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these dragons is the strongest in the Runescape game?",
        "correct_answer": " Black Dragon",
        "answer_a": " Red Dragon",
        "answer_b": " Blue Dragon",
        "answer_c": " Black Dragon",
        "answer_d": " Green Dragon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these Runescape creatures drops a Dragon 2H Sword?",
        "correct_answer": " Chaos Elemental",
        "answer_a": " Mithral Dragon",
        "answer_b": " King Black Dragon",
        "answer_c": " Chaos Elemental",
        "answer_d": " Calphite Queen"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the city in Runescape that you unlock after the Lost City Quest?",
        "correct_answer": " Zanaris",
        "answer_a": " Falador",
        "answer_b": " Zanaris",
        "answer_c": " Catherbys",
        "answer_d": " Camalot"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is the postal service in Runescape?",
        "correct_answer": " RPDT",
        "answer_a": " NYER",
        "answer_b": " LPOG",
        "answer_c": " LAPD",
        "answer_d": " RPDT"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Runescape game you get a fishing skillcape in the Legends Guild.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many forms does the Calphite Queen have in the game Runescape?",
        "correct_answer": " 2",
        "answer_a": " 5",
        "answer_b": " 4",
        "answer_c": " 2",
        "answer_d": " 3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these pets can you own in Runescape?",
        "correct_answer": " Kitten",
        "answer_a": " Hamster",
        "answer_b": " Kitten",
        "answer_c": " Dog",
        "answer_d": " Bird"
    },
    {
        "question": "You can own a pet rock in the Runescape game.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the action/adventure game Killer7, the name of the assassin who can change between seven deadly personalities is Harman Smith.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which persona from the Killer7 game is the one with the Scope on his/her Automatic?",
        "correct_answer": " Kaede",
        "answer_a": " Harman",
        "answer_b": " Con",
        "answer_c": " Dan",
        "answer_d": " Kaede"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Killer7, what is the character Con Smiths\u00e2\u20ac\u2122 age?",
        "correct_answer": " 14",
        "answer_a": " 17",
        "answer_b": " 14",
        "answer_c": " It is not stated.",
        "answer_d": " 25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which voice-over actress, who has also done voices for Nickelodeon, is the voice of Kaede in Killer7?",
        "correct_answer": " Tara Strong",
        "answer_a": " Debby Derryberry",
        "answer_b": " Tara Strong",
        "answer_c": " Lacey Chabert",
        "answer_d": " E.G Daily"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of character Iwazarus ex-wife in the action/adventure game Killer7?",
        "correct_answer": " Mizaru",
        "answer_a": " Mizaru",
        "answer_b": " None of the above",
        "answer_c": " Mizaro",
        "answer_d": " Mizari"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the game Killer7, what is the name of Harmans maid?",
        "correct_answer": " Samantha",
        "answer_a": " Susan",
        "answer_b": " Suzie",
        "answer_c": " Polly",
        "answer_d": " Samantha"
    },
    {
        "question": "The only time you can use the save feature in Killer7 is when character Samantha is in what costume?",
        "correct_answer": " Maid uniform",
        "answer_a": " Tight black overall",
        "answer_b": " Normal clothing",
        "answer_c": " Evening gown",
        "answer_d": " Maid uniform"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was Mask De Smith\u00e2\u20ac\u2122s profession before coming apart of the killers\u00e2\u20ac\u2122 team in Killer7?",
        "correct_answer": " Professional wrestler",
        "answer_a": " Costume artist",
        "answer_b": " Professional boxer",
        "answer_c": " Bodyguard",
        "answer_d": " Professional wrestler"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the action/adventure Killer7, who is the only informant able to contact the Killer7 team?",
        "correct_answer": " Christopher Mills",
        "answer_a": " Kun Lan",
        "answer_b": " Christopher Mills",
        "answer_c": " Heaven Smile",
        "answer_d": " Travis"
    },
    {
        "question": "Besides your Avatar, what other characters can you get at the beginning of the game Baldurs Gate II: Shadows of Amn?",
        "correct_answer": " Imoen, Jahiera, Minsc",
        "answer_a": " Imoen, Jahiera, Minsc",
        "answer_b": " Aerie, Jahiera, Jan",
        "answer_c": " Khalid, Jahiera, Minsc",
        "answer_d": " Valygar, Jahiera, Minsc"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can you get the gauntlets of ogre power in the game Baldurs Gate II: Shadows of Amn?",
        "correct_answer": " The Planar Sphere",
        "answer_a": " The Shadow thieves cellar",
        "answer_b": " The Temple ruins",
        "answer_c": " The Planar prison",
        "answer_d": " The Planar Sphere"
    },
    {
        "question": "What ranger can you save in the game Baldurs Gate II: Shadows of Amn by defeating the Shadow lord in the ruin temple?",
        "correct_answer": " Merella",
        "answer_a": " Merella",
        "answer_b": " Valygar",
        "answer_c": " Minsc",
        "answer_d": " Drizzt"
    },
    {
        "question": "What organization takes Imoen from you, after you escape the first level in the game Baldurs Gate II: Shadows of Amn?",
        "correct_answer": " The Cowled Wizards",
        "answer_a": " The Athkatla Guard",
        "answer_b": " The Emerald warriors",
        "answer_c": " The Shadow Thieves",
        "answer_d": " The Cowled Wizards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who kidnaps Nalia in the game Baldurs Gate II: Shadows of Amn?",
        "correct_answer": " Isaea Roenal",
        "answer_a": " Isaea Roenal",
        "answer_b": " Jon Irenicus",
        "answer_c": " Corieg Axehand",
        "answer_d": " Stumpy Ironfoot"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the 2007 RuneScape Easter special, what item or items do you earn by helping the Easter bunny?",
        "correct_answer": " A chicken suit",
        "answer_a": " An egg that you eat that brings you up one level",
        "answer_b": " A chicken suit",
        "answer_c": " A bunny suit",
        "answer_d": " A ring that transforms you into an egg"
    },
    {
        "question": "What two special benefits do RuneScape members get?",
        "correct_answer": " special tree logs and special locations",
        "answer_a": " rainbow boots and fighting boots",
        "answer_b": " special money and no extra lands",
        "answer_c": " special tree logs and special locations",
        "answer_d": " you can kill demons and go to the barbarian village"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the RuneScape game, it is illegal to use a macroer.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the RuneScape game, the woodcutting skillcape lets you save a bird from a tree.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "On a non-member world in RuneScape, how many places can you travel to on the ship in Port Sarim?",
        "correct_answer": " 1",
        "answer_a": " 3",
        "answer_b": " 6",
        "answer_c": " 1",
        "answer_d": " 4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What animal is Santa on the 2005 RuneScape Christmas special?",
        "correct_answer": " wolf",
        "answer_a": " polar bear",
        "answer_b": " wolf",
        "answer_c": " reindeer",
        "answer_d": " penguin"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the dog the main character is trying to save in the Dogs Life video game?",
        "correct_answer": " Daisy",
        "answer_a": " Butter",
        "answer_b": " Jesse",
        "answer_c": " Daisy",
        "answer_d": " Katie"
    },
    {
        "question": "What changes on the dog every time you go to a different Poodle Parlour in the video game Dogs Life?",
        "correct_answer": " his collar",
        "answer_a": " his attitude",
        "answer_b": " the markings on his coat",
        "answer_c": " his collar",
        "answer_d": " his leash"
    },
    {
        "question": "At what location do you first have to run away from the dog catcher in the Dogs Life video game?",
        "correct_answer": " Village center",
        "answer_a": " Boom City Park",
        "answer_b": " Lake Minniwahwah Cafe",
        "answer_c": " Village center",
        "answer_d": " Farmhouse"
    },
    {
        "question": "When you pick up scents in the game Dogs Life, which of the following is not part of a competition with another dog?",
        "correct_answer": " Barking competition",
        "answer_a": " Marking territory",
        "answer_b": " Barking competition",
        "answer_c": " Digging holes",
        "answer_d": " Doing tricks"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the names of Miss Peaches henchmen in the Dogs Life game?",
        "correct_answer": " Wayne and Dwayne",
        "answer_a": " Wayne and Dwayne",
        "answer_b": " Bob and Rob",
        "answer_c": " Ryan and Bryan",
        "answer_d": " John and Ron"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Dogs Life video game, what challenge do the purple scents start?",
        "correct_answer": " Collect them all before time runs out",
        "answer_a": " Obtain more territory than the other dog",
        "answer_b": " Dig holes faster than the other dog",
        "answer_c": " Collect them all before time runs out",
        "answer_d": " Get all the food before the other dog does"
    },
    {
        "question": "What improves your speed, stamina, and health in the game Dogs Life?",
        "correct_answer": " bones",
        "answer_a": " bones",
        "answer_b": " washing",
        "answer_c": " people",
        "answer_d": " collars"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT found at the grooming parlour in the video game Dogs Life?",
        "correct_answer": " shaver",
        "answer_a": " scissors",
        "answer_b": " shower head",
        "answer_c": " shaver",
        "answer_d": " a sponge"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many places can you go to by train in the Dogs Life game?",
        "correct_answer": " 3",
        "answer_a": " 3",
        "answer_b": " 5",
        "answer_c": " 50",
        "answer_d": " 7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the radio show in the game Dogs Life?",
        "correct_answer": " The Loud Brothers Live",
        "answer_a": " Lake Minniwahah Chat",
        "answer_b": " Miss Peaches Radio Show",
        "answer_c": " Blues, Smooths, and Clues Live",
        "answer_d": " The Loud Brothers Live"
    },
    {
        "question": "What button do you press to dig in Dogs Life (PS2)?",
        "correct_answer": " Circle",
        "answer_a": " Cross",
        "answer_b": " Square",
        "answer_c": " Triangle",
        "answer_d": " Circle"
    },
    {
        "question": "What color is Miss Peaches hair in the video game Dogs Life?",
        "correct_answer": " Orange",
        "answer_a": " Orange",
        "answer_b": " Brown",
        "answer_c": " Blonde",
        "answer_d": " Black"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the Lucky 7s Machine located in the game Dogs Life?",
        "correct_answer": " Lake Minniwahwah Cafe",
        "answer_a": " Lake Minniwahwah Slopes",
        "answer_b": " Lake Minniwahwah Hotel",
        "answer_c": " Lake Minniwahwah Mountain Top",
        "answer_d": " Lake Minniwahwah Cafe"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Dogs Life video game, what is the name of the group of bandits at Boom City?",
        "correct_answer": " The Sleeping Bandits",
        "answer_a": " The Sleeping Bandits",
        "answer_b": " The Danger Bandits",
        "answer_c": " The Ruthless Bandits",
        "answer_d": " The Masked Bandits"
    },
    {
        "question": "What color is the jacket the girl wants you to get from the ski slopes in the video game Dogs Life?",
        "correct_answer": " yellow",
        "answer_a": " black",
        "answer_b": " white",
        "answer_c": " yellow",
        "answer_d": " red"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Dogs Life video game, what does the girl NOT ask you to bring to make her snowman?",
        "correct_answer": " a scarf",
        "answer_a": " a scarf",
        "answer_b": " a hat",
        "answer_c": " twigs",
        "answer_d": " coal"
    }
]